<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Events</title>
    <link>http://www.choosechicago.com//visitors-and-residents/calendar-of-events/</link>
    <description>Events</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 22:24:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>100 100s on the One and a Half</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/100-100s-on-the-One-and-a-Half/24087/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 08-24-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Shane Huffman is swimming to the Moon. If ignorance of the laws of nature is the basis of superstition, there's an element of deliberate superstition in Huffman's willful revision of cosmic order. Huffman reinvests interplanetary space, drained of mystery by the imposed order of cosmological description, with something &amp;quot;extra and other.&amp;quot; Using photography as an investigative process that works with three core phenomena, light, space-time and movement, he explores the individual as a participator in cosmic order rather than mere observer and parasite in &lt;i&gt;100 100s on the One and a Half: Shane Huffman&lt;/i&gt;. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Michigan Ave. Galleries on the 1st Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addendum</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Addendum/24712/</link>
      <description>07-25-2014 to 08-15-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Chicago Artists Coalition presents &lt;i&gt;Addendum&lt;/i&gt;, a group exhibition in association with the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.soapfactory.org/"&gt;Soap Factory&lt;/a&gt; as part of the Coalition's Midwest Artist Exchange.  &lt;i&gt;Addendum&lt;/i&gt; will comprise, per definition, the things which must be added, suggesting that the originating exhibition was neither complete, fixed or perfect. Far from it, in fact, as , , , (pronounced &amp;quot;comma comma comma&amp;quot;) asked of its artists to experiment, embrace uncertainty and trust the potential of their work in the context of a multi-dimensional group exhibition that could never speak fully to each artist's complex and rigorous practice. &lt;i&gt;Addendum&lt;/i&gt; begins to do just that by including, ad hoc, additional images, objects, gestures and performance that provide a more complete representation of many of the artists that made up the , , , exhibition, while simultaneously further problematizing the original survey.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo:&amp;nbsp;Once Around, Peter Happel Christian, 2014, bundle of 365 sheets of gelatin silver paper, rope, one calendar year (Jan. 1, 2013 - Dec.31, 2014)&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adelheid Mers: Enter the Matrix</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Adelheid-Mers-Enter-the-Matrix/24088/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 08-24-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
From studio critique, a mode of conversation about art works, Adelheid Mers has evolved a generative, productive method of talking about other issues as well, by diagramming them onto her Fractal 3-Line Matrix. In this exhibit, &lt;i&gt;Adelheid Mers: Enter the Matrix&lt;/i&gt;, she presents diagrams of conversations with artists about their work, visualizations of arts ecologies and the first iteration of Face Cloud, a cooperation with programmer Robert Woodley. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Blank Matrix Whiteboards will be available for ad hoc diagramming sessions with the public in the adjacent Garland Gallery. Mers will also utilize Garland Gallery as an open studio. Through her residency project, Mers invites the public to participate in her artistic process.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Michigan Ave. Galleries on the 1st Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN GONE ~ Miller &amp; Shellabarger</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/AGAIN-GONE-Miller-Shellabarger/24089/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 08-24-2014 - In &lt;i&gt;AGAIN GONE ~ Miller &amp;amp; Shellabarger&lt;/i&gt;, Miller &amp;amp; Shellabarger use gunpowder and black oil sunflower seeds to outline their bodies and hands. Both materials hold immense amounts of energy, even when distilled into diminutive containers, and are utilized for their rich metaphorical connotation. One is used to feed the flame. The other is left as feed. The flash of gunpowder produces an afterimage, visible not when closing one's eyes, but sprawled out across paper. The explosive marks of smoke and flame trace that which is gone. &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Michigan Ave. Galleries on the 1st Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ann Worthing - All is Beauty</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Ann-Worthing-All-is-Beauty/24798/</link>
      <description>07-18-2014 to 08-22-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The colorful flourishes and calm spaces in &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.annworthing.com/"&gt;Ann Worthing&lt;/a&gt;'s paintings invite a unique sort of looking that allows the viewer to explore and discover each individual world with the curiosity of an aimless wanderer. Landscapes unfold slowly as different textures, figures, and gestures flicker into and out of view, and the viewer's presence in the space shifts between individual and communal; the wanderer is at once a single unit in a network of other separate fragments, and a thread in a fluid, dynamic whole. From this duality, the paintings gain asense of constant movement, where even the most serene and static elements--tree trunk, country road, horizon--refuse stillness.  Each form appears to move at its own pace, and the viewer remains free to navigate the dips and turns at a different speed altogether.  Rather than producing discord, this freedom of movement encourages a subtle yet powerful fluidity, which ultimately creates in each piece a cohesive cadence.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Packer Schopf Gallery&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apes of Wrath</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Apes-of-Wrath/24507/</link>
      <description>06-21-2014 In the world of high stakes, we become a more heightened version of ourselves, which can sometimes resemble more simian behavior than human. From unitard sporting performance artists, an intimate encounter with robot culture and the primal effects of downsizing, &lt;i&gt;Apes of Wrath&lt;/i&gt; embraces the dark and light sides of our human devolution.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Veteran Chicago-based director &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/2034/"&gt;Jen Ellison&lt;/a&gt; leads returning cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1794/"&gt;Carisa Barreca&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1793/"&gt;Brooke Breit&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1835/"&gt;Punam Patel&lt;/a&gt; with new cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/2035/"&gt;Eddie Mujica&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/2086/"&gt;Asher Perlman&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1988/"&gt;Tim Ryder&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1743/"&gt;Alex Kliner&lt;/a&gt; is back at the piano as the Musical Director and Composer and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1392/"&gt;Kyle Anderson&lt;/a&gt; returns as Stage Manager. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of The Second City. Credit:&amp;nbsp;Todd Rosenberg &lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandits &amp; Heroes, Poets &amp; Saints</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Bandits-Heroes-Poets-Saints/24043/</link>
      <description>05-09-2014 to 08-17-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Bandits &amp;amp; Heroes, Poets &amp;amp; Saints: Popular Art of the Northeast of Brazil&lt;/i&gt; tells the story of how African, European and indigenous cultural traditions have interacted over a period of more than 500 years to form the distinctive culture of this fascinating area of the largest country in South America. Brazil is home to one of the largest populations of African descendants in the world, with more than 75 million people. Currently, most of Brazil's population lives in the Northeast of Brazil where centuries of African, European, and Amerindian cultures have mingled to create a mixture of conventions that help in shaping Latin American heritage. &lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Exhibit Segments&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Bandits &amp;amp; Heroes, Poets &amp;amp; Saints&lt;/i&gt; includes nearly 200 works of art by more than 50 artists. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;The first segment, &lt;b&gt;The Land and Its People&lt;/b&gt;, reflects on the history of slavery in Brazil, from the rich plantations that produced a wealthy amount of agricultural produce along the coast to the rugged landscape of the inhospitable dry backlands of the fugitive slave communities.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;The second segment, &lt;b&gt;Expressions of Faith&lt;/b&gt;, explores the African-Brazilian religion of Candomble which combines traditional African roots and Roman Catholicism, while also exploring the evangelical faith of the Northeast.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;The third segment, &lt;b&gt;Poetry, Celebration and Song&lt;/b&gt;, focuses on folk legends and popular festivals of the Nordestinos (People of the Northeast). Also featured in this segment is Literature de Cordel (Literature on a String), which is a popular form of poetry, retelling stories and legends.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Harvest Film Festival</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Black-Harvest-Film-Festival/22065/</link>
      <description>08-01-2014 to 08-28-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Black Harvest Film Festival is our city's largest and longest-running Black film festival and the Gene Siskel Film Center's most vibrant annual showcase featuring provocative films that tell stories, spark lively discussions, and address issues relating to the experiences from the African diaspora. A number of films are made by Chicago directors and feature post-show Q&amp;amp;As.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact: Black Harvest Film Festival celebrates its 20th year in 2014! &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMO Harris Chicago Works: Zachary Cahill</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/BMO-Harris-Chicago-Works-Zachary-Cahill/23484/</link>
      <description>04-29-2014 to 09-28-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
For his exhibit, Cahill presents &lt;i&gt;Snow:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;USSA 2012: The Wellness Center&lt;/i&gt;, the third phase of his project exploring the role institutions play in society. His earlier parts include&lt;i&gt; USSA 2012: The Orphanage Project&lt;/i&gt; (2011), where he re-imagined an orphanage and a gift shop, &lt;i&gt;USSA 2012: The People's Palace's Gift Shop&lt;/i&gt; (2012), and a site-specific banner project &lt;i&gt;USSA 2012: Wellness Center: Idyllic -- affair of the heart&lt;/i&gt; (2013). &lt;i&gt;For Snow&lt;/i&gt;, Cahill approximates a turn of the century sanatorium somewhere in northern Europe. Visitors are invited to enter an actual and fictional space divided into three sections -- a welcome center, a library, and an art gallery -- where Cahill's paintings, sculptures, and writings explore psychological states. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
By simulating a place of refuge within the museum, &lt;i&gt;Snow&lt;/i&gt; navigates the costs and benefits of social withdrawal as necessitated by individual or collective trauma. Drawing on a variety of source material, including Thomas Mann's novel &lt;i&gt;The Magic Mountain&lt;/i&gt;; the Outlook Hotel from Stanley Kubrick's film adaptation of Stephen King's novel &lt;i&gt;The Shining&lt;/i&gt;; and the tradition of Northern Romantic and German Expressionist painting, Cahill considers the role of art in society at the beginning of the 21st century. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: Zachary Cahill, The Future, 2013. Courtesy of the artist and USSA 2012.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabaret Lunch Cruises – Spirit of Chicago</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Cabaret-Lunch-Cruises-Spirit-of-Chicago/24431/</link>
      <description>06-24-2014 to 08-26-2014 - This two-hour cruise along Chicago's magnificent lakefront is perfect for an afternoon getaway, a birthday, church group, entertaining out-of-town guests, you name it.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Enjoy this truly interactive entertainment experience with the Spirit of Chicago Cabaret Show. They will delight you with a broad repertoire - everything from sing-along show tunes to jazz standards. Along the way they will incorporate fascinating facts about the famous Chicago skyline. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Entertainment Cruises &amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte Salomon: Life? Or Theater?</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Charlotte-Salomon-Life-Or-Theater/24442/</link>
      <description>06-19-2014 to 09-21-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
In the early years of World War II, Charlotte Salomon - a 23-year-old Jewish artist from Berlin - fled to the south of France where she shut herself into a hotel room and spent two years feverishly painting the history of her life. She called it &lt;i&gt;Life? or Theater?: A Play With Music&lt;/i&gt;, an astounding body of over 1,300 powerfully drawn and expressively colored gouache paintings conceived as an operetta on paper. Salomon used images, musical cues, dialogue and commentary to tell a compelling coming-of-age story set amidst increasing Nazi oppression. Shortly after completing &lt;i&gt;Life? or Theater?&lt;/i&gt;, the pregnant 26-year-old was transported to Auschwitz and killed. Her singular creation and only major work survived and stands as a testament to Salomon's life and artistic vision.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition of nearly 300 paintings from &lt;i&gt;Life? or Theater?&lt;/i&gt; offers a rare, first-hand opportunity to witness this amazing masterpiece.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Collection Jewish Historical Museum, Amsterdam. Charlotte Salomon Foundation. Charlotte Salomon&amp;reg;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte's Web</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Charlottes-Web/23899/</link>
      <description>07-11-2014 to 08-17-2014 - The favorite on every child's bookshelf, &lt;i&gt;Charlotte's Web&lt;/i&gt;, comes to the stage! When Wilbur is saved and sent to live on farm, he finds a new unexpected family. Follow this piggy hero as he grows from being the runt of the litter to &amp;quot;Some Pig&amp;quot; with the help of a remarkable spider, Charlotte. Join Wilbur, Charlotte, Templeton the Rat, and all the farmyard friends at the State Fair this summer in &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.emeraldcitytheatre.com/"&gt;Emerald City Theatre&lt;/a&gt;'s &lt;i&gt;Charlotte's Web&lt;/i&gt;!</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHGO DSGN</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/CHGO-DSGN/24083/</link>
      <description>05-31-2014 to 11-02-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;CHGO DSGN: Recent Object and Graphic Design. Curated by Rick Valicenti.  &lt;/i&gt;is a major exhibition of recent object and graphic design by 100+ of the city's leading designers. Chicago has long been regarded as an international center for design, and this retrospective celebrates the region's creative and innovative spirit. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Exhibit Hall on the 4th Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;CENTRAL STANDARD TIMING, CST-01 Wristwatch &lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;CODY HUDSON, Vibes Melt Down 2043&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;ROMAIN ANDR&amp;Eacute; AND MICHAEL SAVONA, The Way of the Shovel Scratch-off Poster.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Images courtesy MCA Chicago. Mark Dion, Shovel illustration on the top layer, and Tony Tasset, uncovered photograph.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;MATT WIZINSKY, CloudWriter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Cubs v Milwaukee Brewers</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Cubs-v-Milwaukee-Brewers/23149/</link>
      <description>08-11-2014 to 08-14-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
See the Chicago Cubs play against the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://milwaukee.brewers.mlb.com/index.jsp?c_id=mil"&gt;Milwaukee Brewers&lt;/a&gt; August 11-14 at The Friendly Confines!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Celebrate Wrigley Field's 100th Birthday&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The 2014 season marks Wrigley Field's 100th birthday! The team will celebrate the ballpark's rich century of history during 10 decade-themed homestands complete with historic player uniforms, specialty food offerings, promotional items and entertainment. Go to &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.mlb.com/chc/wrigleyfield100/"&gt;WrigleyField100.com&lt;/a&gt; to learn more. Festivities include:&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Wrigley Field's 100 Great Moments presented by Budweiser&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Historic Bobbleheads&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Throwback Uniforms&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Retro Toys&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://chicago.cubs.mlb.com/chc/ticketing/specialevents.jsp"&gt;Special Events Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Dining Through the Decades&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Historic Guests and Game Entertainment&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://chicago.cubs.mlb.com/chc/fan_forum/cubs_authentics.jsp"&gt;Ballpark&amp;nbsp;D&amp;eacute;cor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Commemorative Ticket Designs&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Farmers Markets</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Farmers-Markets/21668/</link>
      <description>05-10-2014 to 10-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Our city's neighborhoods host annual farmers markets May to October! With each location offering various fruits, vegetables, plants, flowers and more, there's a market for everyone to enjoy. Check the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/dca/supp_info/farmers_market0.html"&gt;Seasonality Chart&lt;/a&gt; to see when your favorite produce is available!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Community Markets&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
New for 2014, some markets will become Community Markets. This is a new concept being introduced, as a market is reflective of the neighborhood it serves. Each market will have what you would expect at a typical farmers market with items like fresh produce, with the addition of music programming and non-food vendors like local artisans - adding a unique vibe to each market and expanding the neighborhood's cultural assets.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Night Markets&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
These will be unique, multi-faceted events which will include live performances and arts &amp;amp; crafts, with local artisans and local restaurants participating. &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Tuesday: Fulton Randolph Market District/Union Park Community Market&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Wednesday: Devon Night Market&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Thursday: Argyle Night Market&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Downtown Markets&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Tuesday: Federal Plaza, Museum of Contemporary Art&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Thursday: Daley Plaza, Willis Tower&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Neighborhood Markets&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Tuesday: Columbus Park, Lincoln Square, Fulton Randolph District/Union Park Community Market&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Wednesday: La Follette Park, Pullman, Devon Community Night Market, Ford City Mall&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Thursday: Argyle Night Market, Austin Town Hall, Hyde Park&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Saturday: Bridgeport, Englewood/Anchor House, Division Street, Lincoln Park, North Center, Printers Row, Southport Market, West Humboldt Park&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Sunday: Beverly, South Shore - Rainbow Beach Park, Garfield Park Conservatory &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;City of Chicago, Department of Cultural Affairs and Special Events&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Landmarks Before the Lens</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Landmarks-Before-the-Lens/18473/</link>
      <description>12-08-2011 to 12-31-2020 - This ongoing exhibition&amp;nbsp;presented by the Commission on Chicago Landmarks features 72 black and white photographs of 24 landmarks and historic districts by Richard Nickel, Barbara Crane, Bob Thall, and Stephen Beal.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Shakespeare in the Parks</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Shakespeare-in-the-Parks/19626/</link>
      <description>07-18-2014 to 08-17-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Chicago Shakespeare Theater presents &lt;i&gt;A Midsummer Night's Dream &lt;/i&gt;for its 2014 Chicago Shakespeare in the Parks season!&amp;nbsp;A specially equipped truck will roll into parks around the city, a stage will unfold, and a company of professional actors will share the delight of Shakespeare with families and neighbors of all ages. &#xD;
In its third year, Chicago Shakespeare in the Parks returns to 18 communities, truly establishing the program as a Chicago summer tradition.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
In&lt;i&gt; A Midsummer Night's Dream&lt;/i&gt;, a popular Shakespearean comedy, a quartet of mismatched lovers, a gaggle of hapless actors and mischievous sprites cross paths with the king and queen of the fairies, entangled in their own domestic dispute. Audiences will be transported to an extraordinary wood brimming with paramours and possibilities where the inexplicable magic of falling in love-and the wonder of waking up from the sweetest of dreams-is discovered.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This tour is made possible by a partnership between Chicago Shakespeare Theater, the City of Chicago, Chicago Park District, Boeing and BMO Harris Bank.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoshakes.com/plays_and_events/parks2014/parks2014whereandwhen"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 18-19: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.navypier.com/about/ov_gateway.html"&gt;Gateway Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 20: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/garfield-park-conservatory/"&gt;Garfield Park Conservatory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 22: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Tuley-Park/#.U3okDihDNSY"&gt;Tuley Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 23-24: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Dvorak-Park/"&gt;Dvorak Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 25-26: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Loyola-Park/"&gt;Loyola Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 27: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/washington-park/"&gt;Washington Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 29: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Riis-Park/"&gt;Riis Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 30: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Piotrowski-Park/"&gt;Piotrowski Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 31: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Gage-Park/"&gt;Gage Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 1: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Hamilton-Park/"&gt;Hamilton Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 2-3: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/wilson-frank-j-park/"&gt;Frank J. Wilson Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 6-7: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/humboldtpark/"&gt;Humboldt Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 8-9: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Welles-Park/"&gt;Welles Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 10: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/columbus-park/"&gt;Columbus Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 12: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Marquette-Park/"&gt;Marquette Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 13: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Ridge-Park/"&gt;Ridge Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 14-15: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Ridge-Park/#.U3olLihDNSY"&gt;South Shore Cultural Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 16-17: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Eckhart-Park/"&gt;Eckhart Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos by Chuck Osgood&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago: City of Big Data</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-City-of-Big-Data/24752/</link>
      <description>06-19-2014 to 10-01-2015 - Did you know data has become a 21st century design material? Architects, planners, engineers and citizens increasingly use data to understand urban issues and spark design innovation. This explosion of digital information, known as &amp;quot;Big Data,&amp;quot; encompasses everything from data collected by environmental sensors to messages on social media. This new exhibition reveals the potential of urban data and offers a new perspective on Chicago and cities everywhere. Visitors can explore interactive displays, recreated sections of the city and get unique views into your own personal data. &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Chicago Architecture Foundation&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicagoisms</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicagoisms/23889/</link>
      <description>04-05-2014 to 01-04-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Throughout its history the city of Chicago has inspired myriad urban and architectural innovations, many of which have had far-reaching influence. The collection of the Art Institute's Department of Architecture has extensive holdings on work within the region of Chicago, representing the important innovations, theoretical approaches, and architectural movements spurred by the city's development. This exhibition surveys Chicago's rich urban history and explores contemporary approaches to five Chicagoisms-key historical principles that have powered the city's distinctive evolution.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Installation view of Chicagoisms at the Art Institute of Chicago, April 5, 2014-January 4, 2015.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Lights Night Tour</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/City-Lights-Night-Tour/24322/</link>
      <description>05-01-2014 to 09-30-2014 - The City Lights Night Tour allows passengers to view the city at night in all of its lit up glory. Highlights will include the John Hancock Building, &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/things-to-do/tours-and-attractions/millennium-park/"&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/articles/view/NAVY-PIER-DAZZLES-DAY-AND-NIGHT/84/"&gt;Navy Pier&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/neighborhoods-and-communities/intro/magnificent-mile/"&gt;Magnificent Mile&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossings and Dwellings</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Crossings-and-Dwellings/24758/</link>
      <description>07-19-2014 to 10-19-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Using art, historical maps, broadsheets, books, liturgical objects, and textiles, &lt;i&gt;Crossings and Dwellings: Restored Jesuits, Women Religious, American Experience, 1814-2014&lt;/i&gt; tells the story of 19th-century European Jesuits and women religious who arrived on the country's expanding western frontier to serve both indigenous and immigrant populations. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition includes liturgical and educational treasures, such as globes by Willem Jansz Blaeu (Dutch, 1571-1638), drawings by Nicolas Point, S.J. (French, 1799-1868), maps by Pierre Jean De Smet, S.J. (Belgian, 1801-1873), the chalice of S&amp;eacute;bastien-Louis Meurin, S.J. (French, 1707-1777), a cope made by St. Rose Philippine Duchesne, RSCJ (French, 1769-1852), and vestments created by indigenous people and presented to De Smet. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The exhibition will also examine the pioneering role of the Religious of the Sacred Heart (RSCJ) and the Sisters of Charity of the Blessed Virgin Mary (BVM) in building Chicago educational institutions, including several schools in Holy Family Parish, Immaculata High School, and Mundelein College.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Crossings and Dwellings&lt;/i&gt; commemorates both the 200th anniversary of the Restoration of the Society of Jesus (1814-2014) and a century of women's education at Loyola-Mundelein (1914-2014).&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depraved New World</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Depraved-New-World/23351/</link>
      <description>03-27-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Ever wonder what people are really thinking? Maybe its positive and sweet. Maybe its weird and dirty. From musical orgies, blind dates and the innocent beginning of an international email scam, &lt;i&gt;Depraved New World&lt;/i&gt; takes you on a wild ride to see what's happening behind the eyes of the beholder. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Returning to The Second City Mainstage, prolific Jeff Award-winning director &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1980/"&gt;Mick Napier&lt;/a&gt; leads returning cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1515/"&gt;Steve Waltien&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1735/"&gt;Tawny Newsome&lt;/a&gt; with new cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1977/"&gt;Chelsea Devantez&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1978/"&gt;John Hartman&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1550/"&gt;Mike Kosinski&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1979/"&gt;Emily Walker&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1981/"&gt;Jesse Case&lt;/a&gt; takes his place behind the piano as the new Musical Director and Composer and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/113/"&gt;Craig Taylor&lt;/a&gt; returns to the booth as Stage Manager.  &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos by TODD ROSENBERG&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destination Solar System</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Destination-Solar-System/23847/</link>
      <description>05-16-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Destination Solar System&lt;/i&gt; is a live show that takes adventurous space explorers on an immersive tour of the Solar System. Set in the future, &lt;i&gt;Destination Solar System&lt;/i&gt; flies audiences from one end of the Solar System to the other in under 30 minutes! From sizzling solar flares on the Sun to liquid methane lakes on Saturn's moon, Titan, tours to the hottest hot spots and the coldest, stormiest and most spectacular sights in the Solar System will launch daily from the Adler's &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.adlerplanetarium.org/shows/"&gt;Grainger Sky Theater&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Adler Planetarium&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthly Delights</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Earthly-Delights/23485/</link>
      <description>06-28-2014 to 11-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Earthly Delights&lt;/i&gt; features the work of artists who rejected one of the central tenets of modernism - the elimination of content and external references - in favor of embracing the decorative, feminine, and playful. This irreverence takes a variety of forms. Swiss artist Balthus remained a committed realist, even though he worked during the time of Surrealism. Michelangelo Pistoletto turned to history painting, intentionally referencing styles and forms considered pass&amp;eacute;. Lynda Benglis, challenged the feminist movement and persisted in the production of non-representative sculpture rather than painting. Carol Bove and Marc Camille Chaimowicz produced objects that exuded sensuality and intimacy; while Nick Cave, Lari Pittman, and Yinka Shonibare exhibit a visible reverence for the popular, accessible, and decorative. Despite the frivolity and humor present in these works, many of the artists exhibited are deeply involved with issues of gender, identity, and politics. This is not 'art for art's sake,' but a belief in the transcendent power of beauty.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago. Lari Pittman, Untitled #14, 2003. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, Joseph and Jory Shapiro Fund by exchange.&amp;copy; 2003 Lari Pittman Photo: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enduring Style: Practice Makes Perfect</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Enduring-Style-Practice-Makes-Perfect/24682/</link>
      <description>06-11-2014 to 09-05-2014 - Willis Tower is currently holding its first fashion exhibition, &lt;i&gt;Enduring Style: Practice Makes Perfect&lt;/i&gt;, in partnership with the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.colum.edu/Admissions/Programs/Fashion.php"&gt;Fashion Studies Department at Columbia College Chicago&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Located in the ground floor lobby of Willis Tower, the exhibition showcases:&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;38 fashion ensembles enhanced by 14 large-scale fashion photographs&lt;/b&gt; focusing on the enduring nature of high-quality design&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Columbia College's partnership with the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://eyeonindia.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eye on India Festival&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, adds &lt;b&gt;three towering 23-foot santos figures showcasing 18&lt;/b&gt; zero-waste, modern design interpretations of India's traditional sari. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;All designs are by students and graduates of the Fashion Studies Department.  &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Columbia College Chicago&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight of the Butterflies</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Flight-of-the-Butterflies/23807/</link>
      <description>02-27-2014 to 02-19-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Join the longest insect migration on Earth! &lt;i&gt;Flight of the Butterflies&lt;/i&gt; is an awe-inspiring story of extraordinary animal endurance and human perseverance. The film follows the captivating story of one creature - Dana (Danaus Plexippus) - and three generations of her offspring on their perilous journey from Mexico to Canada. This natural history epic is interwoven with the detective story of a determined scientist's almost 40-year search to find their elusive wintering sites.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;SK Films&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Street Theatre</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Free-Street-Theatre/24283/</link>
      <description>07-10-2014 to 08-18-2014 - Free Street Theater's youth ensembles will create short performances that recreate and/or transform real-life events from each park's history. Using a variety of aesthetic forms - tiny puppet shows, musical numbers, comedic scenes, Free Street will present work that is specific to a particular park's history and place in the community.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funky Turns 40</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Funky-Turns-40/24044/</link>
      <description>06-27-2014 to 10-19-2014 - &lt;i&gt;Funky Turns 40: Black Character Revolution Animation Art From Classic Cartoons of '70s &lt;/i&gt;commemorates the 40th anniversaries of 1970's Saturday Morning cartoons that featured positive Black characters for the first time in television history. The exhibition includes original production cels and drawings used to produce these cartoons. Also included are images from the animated opening to &lt;i&gt;Soul Train&lt;/i&gt; and two of the few Black cast/Black focused animated features that have been produced since the 1970&amp;prime;s, &lt;i&gt;BeBe's Kids&lt;/i&gt; (1992) and &lt;i&gt;Our Friend Martin&lt;/i&gt; (1999).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hebru Brantley: Parade Day Rain</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Hebru-Brantley-Parade-Day-Rain/24084/</link>
      <description>06-14-2014 to 09-23-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Hebru Brantley explores the human experience of emotion in a solo show, &lt;i&gt;Hebru Brantley: Parade Day Rain&lt;/i&gt;. Looking at optimism and pessimism and their place in the journey from Light to Dark through a narrative of his flyboys and girls and a parade, this exhibition of a &amp;quot;float&amp;quot; and multimedia murals and overhead &amp;quot;ceiling&amp;quot; paintings will create an immersive environment for the viewer. Brantley, a &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.choosechicago.com/neighborhoods-and-communities/intro/bronzeville/"&gt;Bronzeville&lt;/a&gt;-native living and working in Chicago, explores personal and cultural memory in his art. Brantley draws influence from an array of pop culture icons, comic book heroes, Japanese anime and the bold aesthetics of street art pioneers Jean Michel Basquiat, Kaws and Keith Haring.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Sidney R. Yates Gallery on the 4th Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Reblando: New Deal Utopias</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Jason-Reblando-New-Deal-Utopias/24091/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 09-22-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Jason Reblando: New Deal Utopias&lt;/i&gt; is a solo show by the Chicago-based photographer. The exhibit examines Franklin Roosevelt's idealistic vision to resettle displaced farmers and poor urban dwellers in model cities. These &amp;quot;Greenbelt Towns&amp;quot; were testing grounds for a new American way of life as envisioned by the short-lived government agency, the Resettlement Administration. The towns were planned communities that embodied the hope that the challenges of the Great Depression could be met in a spirit of cooperation, not individualism. Today we are again struggling through tough economic times - though not as tough as then - and the politics and divisions that produced the Greenbelt Towns still prevail. These photos explore the intersections of politics and place, of the natural world and the built environment, and of the ideal and real. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact: A second exhibit by the artist is on view in the Richard J. Daley Center Pedway, 50 W. Washington Street: &lt;i&gt;Jason Reblando: Our Work&lt;/i&gt;, through September 24.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaume Plensa: 1004 Portraits</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Jaume-Plensa-1004-Portraits/24395/</link>
      <description>06-18-2014 to 12-31-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
In celebration of its 10th anniversary, &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/things-to-do/tours-and-attractions/millennium-park/"&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt; will feature a special installation of work by &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://jaumeplensa.com/"&gt;Jaume Plensa&lt;/a&gt;, the world-renowned sculptor and creator of one of the Park's most prominent attractions, the &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/articles/view/ART-ARCHITECTURE-GARDENS-IN-MILLENNIUM-PARK/889/"&gt;Crown Fountain&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;i&gt;Jaume Plensa: 1004 Portraits&lt;/i&gt; features four large-scale sculpted portraits positioned in the park such that they complement and expand upon the story of the 1000 LED portraits of Chicago residents that illuminate the Crown Fountain. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Installation Highlights&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The first sculpture, &lt;i&gt;Looking Into My Dreams, Awilda&lt;/i&gt;, is made of resin and stands 38 feet tall.  It will be encountered by visitors as they enter the Park at Michigan Avenue &amp;amp; Madison Street.  The work's surreal and majestic presence bridges the frenetic energy and distractions of city life with the tranquility of the park. Magnificent in scale, the piece's beauty, power and serenity encourage viewers to stop and experience a moment of quiet contemplation.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Three cast iron sculptural portraits, titled &lt;i&gt;Laura&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Paula&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Ines&lt;/i&gt;, will be installed in the South Boeing Gallery (immediately east of the Crown Fountain) and stand 18 feet tall. Despite their great materiality, the sculptures have a hologram-like quality. Plensa's serene, dreamlike portraits provide a peaceful counterbalance to the children's boisterous play in fountain.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Carol Fox and Associates&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jellies</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Jellies/18439/</link>
      <description>04-15-2011 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Visit the beautiful and mysterious world of sea jellies and discover the intriguing ways these pulsing, translucent animals survive&amp;mdash;and thrive&amp;mdash;in the world&amp;rsquo;s oceans without blood, bones, or brains.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Jellies Species&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This special exhibition features various sea jellies species, ranging in size and habitat.&amp;nbsp; Here are some that fasincate us:&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blue Blubber Jelly&lt;/b&gt; - they travel very fast, mostly off the coast of Australia, so they can eat more food.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lion's Mane Jelly&lt;/b&gt; - located in open waters of temperate oceans worldwide, their tentacles can reach up to 100 feet long.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spotted Lagoon Jelly &lt;/b&gt;- they stay close to the sunny surface of the Red Sea, Indian and southern Pacific Oceans so their on-board algae can produce food for them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Jellies Stories&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Studying jellies is harder than you may think.&amp;nbsp; It's like finding a contact lens in an ocean.&amp;nbsp; However, there are many things jellies have taught us, which you can learn about in this exhibit.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;University researchers are developing &lt;b&gt;a search and rescue robot for the U.S. Navy&lt;/b&gt; that mimics the movement of jellies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;One type of &lt;b&gt;jelly may be immortal&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;A new treatment has been created for&lt;b&gt; jelly stings&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Crystal jellies &lt;b&gt;light production has been used in biomedicine&lt;/b&gt;, including discoveries in tumor development and Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photos courtesy of John G. Shedd Aquarium&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Found</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Lost-and-Found/23992/</link>
      <description>05-09-2014 to 08-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Center for Intuitive and Outsider Art is excited to present a truly notable exhibition of photography, &lt;i&gt;Lost and Found: The Search for Harry and Edna&lt;/i&gt;. Harry and Edna were everyday people who lived extraordinary lives. They frequented fancy parties. They traveled the world. And they captured it all on film. Half a century later, their journey continued by falling into the hands of Jeff Phillips. Phillips, a Chicago-based photographer, discovered the lives of Harry and Edna in 30 boxes filled with more than a thousand unlabeled Kodachrome slides at a second hand shop in St. Louis. An artist who has always been fascinated by found photographs, he bought them, wondering why these enigmatic family portraits were abandoned. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Lost and Found&lt;/i&gt; is a unique exhibition of photography that tells the story of a social media search party attempting to discover the identities of an anonymous couple who traveled the world more than 50 years ago. This exhibition presents the beauty, humor, and mystery of found photographs and explores the intersection of photography, social media, and our places in history. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos: &amp;copy; Jeff Phillips&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis Comfort Tiffany</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Louis-Comfort-Tiffany/22454/</link>
      <description>09-28-2013 to 01-04-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Richard H. Driehaus Museum debuts its inaugural exhibition, &lt;i&gt;Louis Comfort Tiffany: Treasures from the Driehaus Collection&lt;/i&gt;, featuring works by one of our country's most celebrated artists. View more than 60 objects representing Louis Comfort Tiffany's 50-year career with the Tiffany Glass &amp;amp; Decorating Company and Tiffany Studios as well as other interrelated firms. The exhibition includes Tiffany stained-glass windows, lamps, vases, accessories, and furniture from the Driehaus Collection, displayed together publicly for the first time.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Group of lamps (bird's-eye detail). Photo by John Faier, &amp;copy; The Richard H. Driehaus Museum.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Group of vases. Photo by John Faier, &amp;copy; The Richard H. Driehaus Museum.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Tiffany Glass and Decorating Company (American, est. 1892). Fish table lamp, ca. 1900. Photo by John Faier, &amp;copy; The Richard H. Driehaus Museum.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Tiffany Studios (American, est. 1902). Garden landscape window, 1900-10. Photo by John Faier, &amp;copy; The Richard H. Driehaus Museum.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Tiffany Studios (American, est. 1902). Inkwell box, ca. 1900-10. Photo by John Faier, &amp;copy; The Richard H. Driehaus Museum.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Tiffany Studios (American, est. 1902). Screen (finial detail), early 20th century. Photo by John Faier, &amp;copy; The Richard H. Driehaus Museum.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucy Slivinski - Soul Touch</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Lucy-Slivinski-Soul-Touch/24799/</link>
      <description>07-18-2014 to 08-22-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Sculptor and installation artist &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.lucyslivinski.com/"&gt;Lucy Slivinski&lt;/a&gt; works with found objects to create conceptual spaces of human connection.  Drawing upon ideas of recycling, regeneration, and interconnectedness, the works in &lt;i&gt;Soul Touch&lt;/i&gt; seem at once repelling and inviting, asking the viewer to consider the materials as objects of consumption and waste, but, more importantly, as tools that generate discourse and encourage energetic, physical engagement. In posing complex dynamics such as this, Slivinski's work lends a unique and innovative tint to notions of decay and beauty, promoting neither one nor the other, but rather intertwining and even collapsing the two together.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Using bottles, wire hangers, chairs, mufflers, and a vast array of other found and recycled materials, Slivinski synchronizes the harsh tensions in her work to produce structures and systems that both bend to natural forces and defiantly resist them.  Individual pieces cling together as energetically as they threaten to break apart; materials heap themselves into masses, and at the same time, beg to be unwoven. The works in &lt;i&gt;Soul Touch &lt;/i&gt;demonstrate Slivinski's unique ability to harness opposing forces in the name of balance, and to draw beauty and tenderness from the anonymous and the disposable. &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Packer Schopf Gallery&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LunchBreak Series</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/LunchBreak-Series/20801/</link>
      <description>12-04-2012 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Enjoy live music in the Chicago Cultural Center's Randolph Caf&amp;eacute; on Tuesdays, Thursdays and Fridays!&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/dca/supp_info/lunchbreak_series.html"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to see a complete schedule.&amp;nbsp; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: City of Chicago, Department of Cultural Affairs and Special Events &amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magritte: The Mystery of the Ordinary</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Magritte-The-Mystery-of-the-Ordinary/23348/</link>
      <description>06-24-2014 to 10-13-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Explore the extraordinary images of Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte in the first major museum exhibition to focus on his breakthrough years. It will feature over 100 paintings, collages, drawings, and objects, along with a selection of photographs, periodicals, and early commercial work, that trace the birth of the themes and strategies Magritte would go on to use throughout his long, productive career - and which make his paintings so unforgettable today.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). Time Transfixed (La Dur&amp;eacute;e poignard&amp;eacute;e), 1938. Oil on canvas; 147 &amp;times; 99 cm (57 7/8 &amp;times; 39 in.). The Art Institute of Chicago, Joseph Winterbotham Collection, 1970.426. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). Painted Object: Eye (Objet peint: &amp;OElig;il), 1932/35. Oil on panel glued to wooden base; 27 &amp;times; 24.8 &amp;times; 14.4 cm (10 5/8 &amp;times; 9 3/4 &amp;times; 5 11/16 in.). The Art Institute of Chicago, through prior gift of Arthur Keating, 1989.53. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). The Secret Player (Le Joueur secret), 1927. Oil on canvas; 152 &amp;times; 195 cm (59 13/16 &amp;times; 76 3/4 in.). Royal Museums of Fine Arts, Belgium, Brussels. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). The Lovers (Les Amants), 1928. Oil on canvas; 54 &amp;times; 73.4 cm (21 3/8 &amp;times; 28 7/8 in.). Museum of Modern Art, New York. Gift of Richard S. Zeisler. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). This Is a Piece of Cheese (Ce&amp;ccedil;i est un morceau de fromage), 1936 or 1937. Oil on canvas board, in gilded wooden frame, with glass dome and pedestal; painting: 12.5 x 18.4 cm (4 15/16 x 7 1/4 in.), glass dome and pedestal: h. 31 cm (12 in.), diam. 25 cm (10 in.). The Menil Collection, Houston. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). The Red Model (Le Mod&amp;egrave;le rouge), 1937. Oil on canvas; 183 x 136 cm (72 1/16 x 53 9/16 in.). Museum Boijmans van Beuningen, Rotterdam. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Ren&amp;eacute; Magritte (Belgian, 1898-1967). Youth Illustrated (La Jeunesse illustr&amp;eacute;e), 1937. Oil on canvas; 183 &amp;times; 136 cm (72 1/16 &amp;times; 53 9/16 in.). Museum Boijmans van Beuningen, Rotterdam. &amp;copy; Charly Herscovici - ADAGP - ARS, 2014 &lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCA Screen: Leslie Hewitt</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/MCA-Screen-Leslie-Hewitt/22692/</link>
      <description>05-17-2014 to 08-31-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Untitled (Structures)&lt;/i&gt; is a dual-projection film installation by New York-based artist Leslie Hewitt in collaboration with independent filmmaker and experimental cinematographer Bradford Young. The footage was shot with 35 mm on location in Memphis, Chicago, and Arkansas, in buildings and spaces associated with the Civil Rights Movement and the Great Migration, when an estimated eight million African Americans moved from the South to Northern cities in search of new opportunities. Representing two years of research addressing the perceivable limits of still photography and the photojournalistic forms associated with the era, the work is comprised of a series of non-linear, silent vignettes that point to often unseen private spaces and explore landscape, interiority, and notions of time. For Hewitt the film is about slowing down our perception of time and thinking about the architectural spaces of history that are often forgotten and remain unnamed.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Leslie Hewitt in collaboration with Bradford Young, Untitled (Structures), 2012. Produced by Karin Chien, and commissioned by the Menil Collection, Houston, with the support of Jerean and Holland Chaney, in collaboration with the Des Moines Art Center and the Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago. Additional funding provided by Joseph Chung, Marilyn and Larry Fields, and Elliot and Kimberly Perry. Material support provided by Kodak, Panavision, Harbor Picture Company. Courtesy the artists and Lucien Terras Inc., New York.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennium Park Greeter Tours</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Millennium-Park-Greeter-Tours/19293/</link>
      <description>05-23-2014 to 10-13-2014 - Learn all about the dazzling art and architecture of &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.choosechicago.com/things-to-do/tours-and-attractions/millennium-park/"&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt; during a free 45-minute guided walk with a knowledgeable &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://chicagogreeter.com/"&gt;Chicago Greeter&lt;/a&gt;! Groups depart from the &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/plan-your-trip/visitor-services-and-resources/visitor-centers/"&gt;Visitor Information Center&lt;/a&gt; at the Chicago Cultural Center. No advanced reservations are required.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennium Park Summer Film Series</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Millennium-Park-Summer-Film-Series/22238/</link>
      <description>06-24-2014 to 08-26-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Calling all movie buffs! Head to &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/things-to-do/tours-and-attractions/millennium-park/"&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday evenings this summer to enjoy free movies at the Jay Pritzker Pavilion. It's now home to the latest and most sophisticated outdoor screen with sound projected from the Pavilion's state-of-the-art sound system. The images are bright, clear and visible from the front row to the back of the Great Lawn, so there isn't a bad seat in the park! Be sure to grab a blanket and pack a picnic dinner to enjoy with your friends and family. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact:&amp;nbsp;the screen measures 40 feet long and 22.5 feet high with an LED system and technology that is similar to that of a giant-screen television.  &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;The Movies&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 24: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vntAEVjPBzQ"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ghostbusters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 1: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VN8ze3S0Uj8"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Top Gun&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 8: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tWyUJcA8Zfo"&gt;&lt;i&gt;20 Feet from Stardom&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 15: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eW9Xo2HtlJI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;O Brother, Where Art Thou?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 22: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ut06d4dptWo"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Field of Dreams&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 29: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N63XSUpe-0o"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is Spinal Tap&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 5: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P7FcPlt8hHc"&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Birdcage&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 12: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gx7QdFbxr1c"&gt;&lt;i&gt;American Graffiti&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 19: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IR6mBspK13o"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dreamgirls&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 26: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H_3T4DGw10U"&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Wizard of Oz&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennium Park: An Anatomy in Photographs</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Millennium-Park-An-Anatomy-in-Photographs/24398/</link>
      <description>06-18-2014 to 10-31-2015 - Celebrating the 10th anniversary of &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/things-to-do/tours-and-attractions/millennium-park/"&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt;, this exhibition is curated by John Vinci of &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.vinci-hamp.com/"&gt;Vinci/Hamp Architects&lt;/a&gt; and features over 50 images - including historical photographs; images of the Park before, during and after construction; and the work of numerous photographers who used the Park as their subject.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movies in the Parks - The Blind Side</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Movies-in-the-Parks-The-Blind-Side/24247/</link>
      <description>08-12-2014 to 08-12-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Chicago Park District shows free outdoor movies throughout the summer for free at parks around the city! On August 12, see &lt;i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0878804/"&gt;The Blind Side&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;(PG-13) at &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Ward-A-Montgomery-Park/"&gt;A. Montgomery Ward Park&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Movies in the Parks runs May 29-August 30. &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/assets/1/23/Chicago_Park_District_2014_Movies_Schedule.pdf"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for the complete schedule.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Geographic Presents: Earth Explorers</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/National-Geographic-Presents-Earth-Explorers/23623/</link>
      <description>03-20-2014 to 09-01-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Organized around Earth's spectacular eco-zones - Polar Regions, Oceans, Rain Forests, Mountains and Caves, and the African Savanna - &lt;i&gt;Earth Explorers&lt;/i&gt; brings the unparalleled adventures of National Geographic to life. Learn about the daring men and women who venture into dangerous and remote parts of the world to discover new places, help protect our planet's biodiversity and unearth new scientific discoveries. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;CHILL: The Polar Regions&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Explore an Arctic cabin and test your ability to live in an ice-covered world.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;DIVE: The Oceans&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Descend into the deep ocean in a 3-D submersible and explore how life forms at varying depths, even coming face-to-face with a great white shark.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;TREK: The Rain Forests&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Identify incredible insects from the Amazon while learning the benefits of biodiversity.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;CLIMB: Mountains and Caves&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Ascend into the thin air of the Himalayas.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;SOAR: The Savanna&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Soar in a hot air balloon over the savanna while learning about the life of elephants and other mammals.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: GES Entertainment&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Vaults: World's Fair</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Opening-the-Vaults-Worlds-Fair/20683/</link>
      <description>10-25-2013 to 09-07-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition is a continuation of the popular &lt;i&gt;Opening the Vaults &lt;/i&gt;series. This one provides a never-before-seen glimpse into the Columbian Exposition of 1893, held right here in Chicago! Now 120 years later, the museum is opening its collections to display incredible artifacts from one of the most prominent events in our city's history.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact: the Columbian Exposition of 1893 included the debut of The Field Museum. &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Past Perfect: The Art of Eileen Doman</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Past-Perfect-The-Art-of-Eileen-Doman/24797/</link>
      <description>07-11-2014 to 09-27-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Intuit: The Center for Intuitive and Outsider Art presents a return to Chicago with &lt;i&gt;Past Perfect: The Art of Eileen Doman&lt;/i&gt;. In 1993, Eileen Doman found herself restless. A suburban housewife whose daughter had just begun school, she decided to take up painting. Having no formal training, she drew inspiration from the works of Amedeo Modigliani and Vincent van Gogh, remembering them from a fieldtrip to the Art Institute at age 15. Doman turned to photographs for subjects - painting relatives, friends, and the occasional pop culture celebrity - captured in time on canvas. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Now, more than 20 years later, Intuit is proud to welcome this extraordinary painter back to Chicago. Doman's art, captured through the prism of a modern primitive style and witty intelligence, often presents unanswered questions, offers a quirky glimpse at the past, and provides an artistic satisfaction that is enduring.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Lil, Harry and Doris Scene II, 1992, Acrylic on canvas, 16 x 20 inches (each), Collection of Ellen Hoover and&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Chas Ray Krider&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Mrs. Gray on a Sunday, 1993, Acrylic on canvas, 18 x 14 inches, Louis-Dreyfus Family Collection&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Eileen Doman, The Methodist Couple, 1999, Acrylic on canvas, 24 x 18 inches, Collection of Nannette Maciejunes&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Dreams</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Private-Dreams/24624/</link>
      <description>06-12-2014 to 09-26-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Private Dreams &lt;/i&gt;will feature eight new sculptures from &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://jaumeplensa.com/"&gt;Jaume Plensa&lt;/a&gt;'s iconic series of heads in a range of materials including bronze, glass, and for the first time, volcanic basalt.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Standing six feet tall, the basalt sculptures &lt;i&gt;Paula, Awilda&lt;/i&gt;, and &lt;i&gt;Rui Rui &lt;/i&gt;emerge from stone as Plensa retains sections of the material in their natural, unfinished state. Installed as a group, imposing yet peaceful, the works create a meditative, even spiritual space. Bronze sculptures &lt;i&gt;Rui Rui in Shanghai &lt;/i&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;i&gt;Sanna in Ume&amp;aring; &lt;/i&gt;are some of the artist's first mid-scale works that explore perspective and illusion through the flattening of form, a concept Plensa premiered in his 2013 series of monumental cast iron heads. The sculptures shift from realism to flattened relief depending on the viewing angle. The physicality of the basalt and bronze works is juxtaposed with the remaining two sculptures in the exhibition; small portraits made from Murano glass that are fragile and intimate in both scale and material. In all of the portraits, the girls have their eyes closed - Plensa's conceptual metaphor for dreaming.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
An illustrated catalogue accompanies the exhibition with an essay by Clare Lilley, Director of Programme, Yorkshire Sculpture Park, UK.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Paula, Rui Rui, and Awilda. 2014. Courtesy of Richard Gray Gallery.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railroaders: Jack Delano’s Homefront Photography</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Railroaders-Jack-Delanos-Homefront-Photography/23927/</link>
      <description>04-05-2014 to 08-10-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Chicago History Museum and Center for Railroad Photography and Art present &lt;i&gt;Railroaders: Jack Delano's Homefront Photography&lt;/i&gt;, an exhibition revealing the humanity, heroism, and diversity of the Chicago railroad community whose work was instrumental to the war effort during World War II. In 1942, photographer Jack Delano was tasked by the federal government to capture images of the rail community to rally support for the war effort. The result was three thousand images, many of which highlight Chicago's primacy to the North American rail network. The dignity of everyday work and the stories of individual railroaders and their descendants are explored in more than 60 photographs by Delano. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Exhibition Highlights&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Railroaders transports visitors to the rail yards, the stations, and the roads in an immersive, multi-sensory exhibition. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
In the first section, &lt;b&gt;On the Trains&lt;/b&gt;, visitors will encounter images of freight trains and their crews at work. Ambient sounds associated with preparing the train for the road and the train in motion appear in this section, as well as an environment based on the interior of a train's caboose, often referred to as a mobile office. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The second section, &lt;b&gt;In The Station&lt;/b&gt;, features images of Union Station and station staff, as well as elements of passenger travel. A reproduction of a ticket window is a highlight of this section. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The third and largest section, &lt;b&gt;Around the Yards&lt;/b&gt;, showcases prints of the workers who kept trains running, with photographs organized by each worker's role in maintaining the trains. Biographies of portrait subjects are included in this section, as well as a large scale model train rail yard.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: Delano and his Speed Graphic camera, 1943; Frank Williams, car repairman, Illinois Central's Markham Yard, November 1942; Union Station, 1943; The Sinise crew on the Indiana Harbor Belt, February 1943; Roundhouse at Proviso Yard, December 1942; Dorothy Lucke, engine wiper, C&amp;amp;NW yard, Clinton, Iowa, April 1943&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick Bayless in Cascabel</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Rick-Bayless-in-Cascabel/22918/</link>
      <description>07-30-2014 to 08-31-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Dinner. Daring. Desire. &lt;i&gt;Cascabel&lt;/i&gt; returns in 2014 for a limited engagement at a new venue - &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.goodmantheatre.org/"&gt;Goodman Theatre&lt;/a&gt;! Experience an unforgettable theatrical adventure while enjoying a sumptuous gourmet Mexican feast, world-class circus acts, exhilarating flamenco, hilarious comedy and a tantalizing love story starring celebrity chef &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.rickbayless.com/about/meetrick.html"&gt;Rick Bayless&lt;/a&gt;. Come hungry!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: Darris Lee Harris; Sean Williams&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Agne - Urban Perspectives</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Robert-Agne-Urban-Perspectives/24800/</link>
      <description>07-18-2014 to 08-22-2014 - Approaching both the built environment and the natural world with a logical, mathematical eye, Robert Agne's drawings reveal an intense engagement with, and understanding of, the near-mechanical systematization of the urban landscape.  The works in &lt;i&gt;Urban Perspectives&lt;/i&gt;--awe-inspiring in their order, repetition, and confident cleanliness--reflect the artist's electrical engineering background and early fascination with realism, and in the process, grasp upon the sense of automaton anonymity that often pervades portraits of urban life.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Packer Schopf Gallery&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rush Hour Concerts</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Rush-Hour-Concerts/22070/</link>
      <description>06-03-2014 to 08-26-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Rush Hour Concerts presents its 15th annual Summer Concert Series featuring free concerts of &amp;quot;great music for busy lives&amp;quot; at &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/neighborhoods-and-communities/intro/river-north/"&gt;River North&lt;/a&gt;'s historic St. James Cathedral.  In a format that reinvents classical music for life in a new century, concerts begin with a pre-concert food and beverage reception with the artists in the cathedral foyer, followed by a 30-minute concert.  The reception and concert are always free and no tickets are required!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;June&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;June 3: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.fulcrumpoint.org/"&gt;Fulcrum Point New Music Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Igor Stravinsky: &lt;i&gt;L'Histoire du soldat&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;June 10: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.janetsung.com/"&gt;Janet Sung&lt;/a&gt; (violin) and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.khpiano.net/"&gt;Kuang-Hao Huang&lt;/a&gt; (piano)&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Johannes Brahms: Violin Sonata No. 2 in A major&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;June 17: John Macfarlane (violin), &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://cso.org/About/Performers/Performer.aspx?id=3179"&gt;Brant Taylor&lt;/a&gt; (cello) and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.winstonchoi.com/live/"&gt;Winston Choi&lt;/a&gt; (piano)&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Howard Frazin: &lt;i&gt;Some Thoughts on Good and Evil&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;June 24: Members of the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://cso.org/"&gt;Chicago Symphony&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.lyricopera.org/"&gt;Lyric Opera&lt;/a&gt; Orchestras; John Macfarlane, conductor&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Aaron Copland: &lt;i&gt;Appalachian Spring&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;July&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 1: Liba Schacht (violin), &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.caroljcook.com/"&gt;Carol Cook&lt;/a&gt; (viola) and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://cso.org/About/Performers/Performer.aspx?id=3239"&gt;John Sharp&lt;/a&gt; (cello)&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Ernő Dohn&amp;aacute;nyi': String Trio&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 8: TBA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 15: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.saintjamescathedral.org/about/st-james-staff/mr-bruce-barber/"&gt;Bruce Barber&lt;/a&gt; (organ) and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.sonesdemexico.com/"&gt;Sones de Mexico Ensemble  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;All-Bach Double-Header&amp;quot; featuring Trio Sonata No. 4, Prelude and Fugue in E-flat, and more.  &lt;i&gt;A special one-hour concert dedicated to Founder Deborah Sobol.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 22: &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://cso.org/About/Performers/Performer.aspx?id=3179"&gt;Brant Taylor&lt;/a&gt; (cello) and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.khpiano.net/"&gt;Kuang-Hao Huang&lt;/a&gt; (piano)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	Ludwig van Beethoven: Cello Sonata in D major&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 29: Singers from the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/RyanOperaCenter"&gt;Patrick G. and Shirley W. Ryan Opera Center&lt;/a&gt; at the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.lyricopera.org/"&gt;Lyric Opera of Chicago&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&amp;quot;Lyric Shorts&amp;quot; featuring excerpts from Mozart's &lt;i&gt;Don Giovanni&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;August&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 5:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.quintetattacca.com/"&gt;Quintet Attacca&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Poetry Foundation: &amp;quot;Open Door Encore,&amp;quot; featuring readings of original poetry, composed by area professors and their students, set to music&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 12: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://fifth-house.com/"&gt;Fifth House Ensemble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Trios of Khachatryan and Bart&amp;oacute;k&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 19: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.jasonseedmusic.com/Home.html"&gt;Jason Seed Stringtet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;/b&gt;Rush Hour Concerts 15th Anniversary commissioned World Premiere&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;August 26: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.thirdcoastpercussion.com/"&gt;Third Coast Percussion&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.danschlosbergmusic.com/"&gt;Daniel Schlosberg&lt;/a&gt; (piano) and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://amybriggspiano.com/common.php"&gt;Amy Briggs&lt;/a&gt; (piano)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
	Steve Reich: &lt;i&gt;Sextet&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seadog &amp; Chicago Children’s Museum Package</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Seadog-Chicago-Childrens-Museum-Package/24437/</link>
      <description>06-04-2014 to 10-31-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Seadog Cruises and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagochildrensmuseum.org/"&gt;Chicago Children's Museum&lt;/a&gt; have come together to offer a special Lakefront Speedboat Tour and Museum Admission Package - at a great price.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lakefront Speedboat Tour&lt;/b&gt;: An exciting 30-minute speedboat ride jam-packed with music, entertainment, fun and wide-open views of Chicago's unbelievable skyline.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chicago Children's Museum&lt;/b&gt;: Three floors of awesome exhibits and playful programs that invite kids and their families to splash, climb, build, create, explore and discover.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photo courtesy of Entertainment Cruises &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial Drawings</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Serial-Drawings/24824/</link>
      <description>07-01-2014 to 08-31-2014 - Three sets of works from three generations of artists associated with Chicago explore drawing's expressive or narrative potential through unified cycles of drawings.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Serial Drawings&lt;/i&gt; features figurative works from Robert Barnes, Barbara Rossi, and Robert Lucy. Each artist assumes a different and highly personal approach to the human form. This collection-based exhibition at the Smart Museum of Art reunites ten drawings by Barnes based on Ezra Pound's &lt;i&gt;Cantos&lt;/i&gt; (1961) and also includes Rossi's series &lt;i&gt;Very Rich Hims and Hers&lt;/i&gt; (1970) and Lucy's suite &lt;i&gt;Sea Fashions&lt;/i&gt; (2002-03).  &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simon Starling: Metamorphology</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Simon-Starling-Metamorphology/22693/</link>
      <description>06-07-2014 to 11-02-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Since emerging from the Glasgow art scene in the early 1990s, Simon Starling has established himself as one of the leading artists of his generation, working in a wide variety of media (film, installation, photography) to interrogate the histories of art and design, scientific discoveries, and global economic and ecological issues, among other subjects. The recipient of the 1997 Turner Prize, this is Starling's first major exhibition at an American museum. Starling's working method constitutes recycling, repurposing existing materials for new, artistic aims; retelling existing stories to produce new historical insights; linking, looping, and remaking. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: &lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Simon Starling, Bird in Space, 2004. Image courtesy of the artist and Casey Kaplan, NY.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Simon Starling, Film still, D1 - Z1 (22,686,575:1), 2009. Courtesy of the artist and Casey Kaplan, New York.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Simon Starling, The Long Ton, 2009. Courtesy of the artist and neugerriemschneider, Berlin. Photo: Jens Ziehe.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Simon Starling, Project for a Masquerade (Hiroshima), 2010-11. Rennie Collection, Vancouver. Photo: Anders Sune Berg.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Simon Starling, Flaga 1972-2000 (A Fiat produced in Turin, Italy, in 1974 and customised using parts manufactured and fitted in Poland, following a journey of 1290 km from Turin to Cieszyn), 2002. Fondazione Sandretto Re Rebaudengo, Turin.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Simon Starling, Autoxylopyrocycloboros, 2006. Courtesy of the artist and The Modern Institute, Glasgow.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stingray Touch</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Stingray-Touch/21497/</link>
      <description>05-23-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Feel the wonder and underwater grace of stingrays in a hands-on experience at Shedd Aquarium, &lt;i&gt;Stingray Touch&lt;/i&gt;. Located under a tented structure on the aquarium's south terrace, the 18,000-gallon pool will feature approximately 40 cownose rays (&lt;i&gt;Rhinoptera bonasus&lt;/i&gt;) and yellow rays (&lt;i&gt;Urobatis jamaicensis&lt;/i&gt;). Guests will have exceptional views of the rays' natural behaviors across the 80-foot-long and 22-foot-wide habitat. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact: The diamond-shaped cownose ray glides through the water with a wingspan of up to 3 feet long. &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of John G. Shedd Aquarium&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Evenings at Chicago Botanic Garden</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Summer-Evenings-at-Chicago-Botanic-Garden/21572/</link>
      <description>06-09-2014 to 09-01-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The summer season brings a full schedule of free, live outdoor concerts for all tastes and ages to the Chicago Botanic Garden  Monday - Thursday evenings!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagobotanic.org/carillon"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mondays: Carillon Concerts by the water (June 9 - September 1)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Live music on the lawn by McGinley Pavilion&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Picnic dinners allowed&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Garden Grille preconcert dinner available&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Preconcert carillon tour and demonstration: 5:30 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagobotanic.org/evenings/esplanade_evenings"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tuesdays: Music on the Esplanade and Cocktails (June 10 - August 26)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;A variety of live music (Spanish guitar, blues, jazz)&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Beautiful views and quiet walks through the gardens&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Drinks and a light supper available&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagobotanic.org/interest/music/dancin_sprouts"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wednesdays: Dancin' Sprouts (June 11 - August 27) &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Musical entertainment for kids&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Picknicking allowed on the Esplanade only&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagobotanic.org/interest/music/hot_summer_nights"&gt;Thursdays: Hot Summer Nights Music Series (June 12 - August 28)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagobotanic.org/interest/music/hot_summer_nights"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Dance to high-energy music of diverse genres&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Beverages and light fare will be available for purchase&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Professional instructors teach mini lessons that correspond with the music that evening &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photos: &amp;copy; Chicago Botanic Garden &lt;/i&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surrealism and War</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Surrealism-and-War/24483/</link>
      <description>05-27-2014 to 11-01-2014 - &lt;i&gt;Surrealism and War&lt;/i&gt; includes the seminal work &lt;i&gt;The Earth Lies Screaming&lt;/i&gt; by Jim Leedy, a Korean War veteran who was one of only two Americans invited to participate in the largest Surrealist exhibition ever assembled at the Retretti Art Center, Finland, an exhibition that began with Miro, Dali, and DuChamp, and culminated with several works by Mr. Leedy.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Surrealism is an attempt to revolt against the inherent contradictions of a society ruled by rational thought while dominated by war and oppression. Surrealism seeks expression of thought in the absence of all control exercised by reason and free of aesthetic and moral preoccupation. It is this same absence of control exercised by reason that many combat veterans seek to explore and express after their experiences in war. &lt;i&gt;Surrealism and War &lt;/i&gt;features the artwork of nine veteran artists that intentionally and unintentionally use and explore Surrealist processes and concepts. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Featured artists include Korean War veteran Jim Leedy, Vietnam War veterans William Dugan, Stan Gillett, Michael Helbing, and Richard Yohnka, Gulf War veteran Ehren Tool, Kosovo veteran Giuseppe Pellicano, and Iraq War veterans David Keefe and Robynn Murray.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target Family Fun Festival</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Target-Family-Fun-Festival/21632/</link>
      <description>06-23-2014 to 08-24-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This summer, Millennium Park transforms into a giant play area for kids at the Target Family Fun Festival! Open to families with kids of all ages, this fest is packed with family-friendly interactive activities, arts and crafts and games. All activities take place on the Park's Chase Promenade North.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Festival Highlights&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wiggleworms&amp;reg;&lt;/b&gt; - sing along and dance with instructors from the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.oldtownschool.org/concerts/community/"&gt;Old Town School of Folk Music&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reading Circle&lt;/b&gt; - relax with story time&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Family Performances &lt;/b&gt;- enjoy a mix of live music and interactive dance performances&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Movement Mondays &lt;/b&gt;- get moving with hip hop yoga, tap dance, hoopnotics and much more&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read All About It! &lt;/b&gt;- listen to a special reading of a featured author (first 50 families will receive a free book!) &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Activity Zone Partners&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Partners change weekly and include:&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 23-29: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.luriegarden.org/"&gt;Lurie Garden&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 30 - July 6: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.getoutandgrow.com/"&gt;Get Out &amp;amp; Grow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 7-13: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.barrelofmonkeys.org/"&gt;Barrel of Monkeys&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 14-20: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparent.com/"&gt;Chicago Parent Magazine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 21-27: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.msichicago.org/"&gt;Museum of Science and Industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 28 - August 3:&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagohs.org/"&gt;Chicago History Museum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 4-10: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.easelartstudio.com/#about-us"&gt;Easel Art Studio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 11-17: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://circesteem.org/"&gt;CircEsteem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 18-24: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://lookingglasstheatre.org/"&gt;Lookingglass Theatre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photo credit: City of Chicago, Department of Cultural Affairs and Special Events&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Beauty of Moths</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/The-Hidden-Beauty-of-Moths/23382/</link>
      <description>04-19-2014 to 08-17-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition in the Joutras Gallery will take an exciting, up-close look at the often-unrealized beauty of moths. Artist Joseph Scheer uses a flatbed scanner to document this mysterious beauty; the resulting larger-than-life prints are absolutely stunning. The show includes high-resolution scans of rare and common moths that show magnificent color palettes and highly detailed patterns.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Chicago Botanic Garden photos&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Machine Inside: Biomechanics</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/The-Machine-Inside-Biomechanics/23535/</link>
      <description>03-12-2014 to 01-04-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Investigate the marvels of natural engineering in &lt;i&gt;The Machine Inside: Biomechanics&lt;/i&gt;. Explore how plants and animals stay in one piece despite the crushing forces of gravity, the pressure of water and wind, and the attacks of predators. Using surprising tactics, creatures endure the planet's extreme temperatures, find food against fierce competition, and - without metal, motors or electricity - circulate their own life-sustaining fluids.  &#xD;
Discover how evolution is Earth's greatest innovator, only at The Field Museum.   &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Exhibit Highlights&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&#xD;
	Feel for yourself how hard a giraffe's heart works to pump blood up to its head. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Try to &amp;quot;fly&amp;quot; and study the many different ways creatures jump, gallop, slither, and swim. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;See technological breakthroughs - like Velcro, as well as modern wind turbines and chainsaws - that were inspired by nature's ingenuity. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;&amp;copy; The Field Museum; &amp;copy; Perry Aragon; &amp;copy; Chris Burt / Shutterstock; &amp;copy; www.AlexHyde.co.uk; &amp;copy; Jonas Merian; &amp;copy; Phil Lanoue; &amp;copy; Ron Austing | WildNaturePhotos&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Qualms</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/The-Qualms/21654/</link>
      <description>07-03-2014 to 08-31-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Steppenwolf Theatre Company presents the World Premiere of &lt;i&gt;The Qualms&lt;/i&gt;. At a beachside apartment complex, a group of friends gathers for their regular evening of food, drink, drugs and partner-swapping. When Chris and Kristy attempt to become the newest members, the evening does not go as planned. The artichoke dip grows cold as the party devolves into a territorial battle over mating privileges. Does sex ruin everything? And what is the purpose of monogamy? Bruce Norris's comedy explores the eternal struggle for power, status and getting laid.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact: this play is by Bruce Norris, the Pulitzer Prize-winning author of &lt;i&gt;Clybourne Park&lt;/i&gt;. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Michael Brosilow&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Second City’s Incomplete Guide</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/The-Second-Citys-Incomplete-Guide/23518/</link>
      <description>03-04-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
From the great books to the worst presidents, The Second City has spent half a century laughing in the face of our past, present and future.  And now it's all in one show...sort of.  UP Comedy Club presents &lt;i&gt;The Second City's Incomplete Guide to Everything&lt;/i&gt;, a hilarious collection of scenes and songs that skewers everything that you learned in college - or that you should have learned in college on the days you slept in.  &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: UP Comedy Club&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universe: A Walk through Space and Time</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/The-Universe-A-Walk-through-Space-and-Time/19533/</link>
      <description>07-13-2012 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Adler Planetarium's newest exhibition teaches you all about the Universe. Featuring various multi-media interactive stations, &lt;i&gt;The Universe: A Walk through Space and Time &lt;/i&gt;is a mix of fun and education.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;As you walk through, you'll first learn about the &lt;b&gt;history of the Universe.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp; You're invited to explore the big questions - how large is the Universe?&amp;nbsp; Are we alone?&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Next you'll &lt;b&gt;see the wonders of the Universe&lt;/b&gt; thanks to spectacular overhead projection.&amp;nbsp; You can zoom from one location to another, viewing high resolution images from the world's best telescopes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Your kids can &lt;b&gt;play in interactive stations&lt;/b&gt; too.&amp;nbsp; They can look like an astronaut on the moon.&amp;nbsp; They can also send electronic postcards to themselves from galaxies, traveling at the speed of light. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;The Universe: A Walk through Space and Time&lt;/i&gt; is located in the Adler's newly renovated Pritzker Hall of Cosmology.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Adler Planetarium&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuesdays on the Terrace</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Tuesdays-on-the-Terrace/19413/</link>
      <description>06-03-2014 to 09-09-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Museum of Contemporary Art's Terrace turns into a jazz concert every Tuesday evening starting June 3. Hosted by Al Carter-Bay and Richton Guy Thomas from &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://whpk.org/"&gt;WHPK 88.5fm&lt;/a&gt;, this live entertainment event will let you unwind while enjoying the sounds of Chicago's quintessential jazz musicians outdoors.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Dining Options&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner Buffet created by Puck's Cafe&lt;/b&gt; - features a changing menu with cuisine inspired by picnics, state fairs, and other summertime favorites&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Outdoor grill&lt;/b&gt; - features hamburgers, homemade sausages, and a variety of freshly made salads along with assorted cold beverages, wine, and seasonal cocktails from the cash bar &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;No outside food and beverages allowed&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Performers&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Each week different jazz musicians play at the Terrace.  You can bring your own blanket to watch on the garden lawn, or you can rent a chair.&amp;nbsp; Performers include: &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 3: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-maggie-brown/"&gt;Maggie Brown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 10: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-whirlpool/"&gt;Whirlpool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 17: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-goran-ivanovic-trio/"&gt;Goran Ivanovic Trio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;June 24: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-pat-mallinger-quartet/"&gt;Pat Mallinger Quartet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 1: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-fred-lonberg-holm-2/"&gt;Fred Lonberg-Holm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 8: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-corey-wilkes-2/"&gt;Corey Wilkes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 15: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-jazz-links-ryan-nyther-quartet/"&gt;Ryan Nyther Quartet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 22: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-tomeka-reid/"&gt;Tomeka Reid&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 29: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-dee-alexander-2/"&gt;Dee Alexander&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 5: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-jason-stein-quartet/"&gt;Jason Stein Quartet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 12: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-the-chicago-reed-quartet/"&gt;The Chicago Reed Quartet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 19: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-tatsu-aoki-miyumi-project/"&gt;Tatsu Aoki, Miyumi Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 26: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-mike-reed-people-places-things/"&gt;Mike Reed's People, Places &amp;amp; Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;September 2: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-robert-irving-iii/"&gt;Robert Irving III Quintet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;September 9: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www2.mcachicago.org/event/tuesdays-on-the-terrace-xavier-breaker-coalition/"&gt;Xavier Breaker Coalition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos: &amp;copy; Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago. Photo &amp;copy; Justin Wambold. &lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbound: Contemporary Art after Frida Kahlo</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Unbound-Contemporary-Art-after-Frida-Kahlo/22691/</link>
      <description>05-03-2014 to 10-05-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition features artworks drawn primarily from the MCA Collection that engage with aesthetic issues similar to those explored by Mexican artist Frida Kahlo. Post-colonial feminist artist Frida Kahlo studied gender, the female body, and identity through her paintings, which prominently feature self-portraiture. Through confrontational depictions of the female body, Kahlo transgressed taboos against portraying the female body as more than a passive object of the male gaze. In representing the psychological effects of her physical trauma and her experience in the world, having grown up during the Mexican Revolution, Kahlo used her own figure to undermine and complicate social mores. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
More than 30 other artists in the show explore themes similar to those of Kahlo: the representation and construction of gender, the political or traumatized body, and the contested notion of national identity. The exhibition features works by Louise Bourgeois, Nan Goldin, Felix Gonzalez-Torres, Jos&amp;eacute; Leonilson, Ana Mendieta, Gabriel Orozco, Cindy Sherman, Doris Salcedo, Lorna Simpson, among others. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Daniela Rossell, Untitled (Ricas y famosas) (rooftop), 1999. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, gift of The Disaronno Originale Photography Collection. Photo: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Shirin Neshat, Turbulent, 1998. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, gift of Susan and Lewis Manilow. &amp;copy; 1998 Shirin Neshat.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Shirin Neshat, Turbulent, 1998. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, gift of Susan and Lewis Manilow. &amp;copy; 1998 Shirin Neshat.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Frida Kahlo, La venadita (little deer), 1946. Private collection, Chicago. &amp;copy; 2013 Banco de M&amp;eacute;xico Diego Rivera Frida Kahlo Museums Trust, Mexico, D.F. / Artists Rights Society (ARS), New York.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Lorna Simpson, She, 1992. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, gift of Judith Neisser. &amp;copy; 1992 Lorna Simpson. Photo: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Thomas Houseago, Untitled, 2008. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, gift of Mary and Earle Ludgin by exchange and restricted gift of the Collectors Forum. &amp;copy; 2008 Thomas Houseago. Photo: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under The Picasso</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Under-The-Picasso/24540/</link>
      <description>05-14-2014 The Department of Cultural Affairs and Special Events presents FREE cultural programs year round at the Daley Civic Center. The &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/dca/supp_info/under_the_picassoschedule.html"&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt; is posted each month so check back often!&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of City of Chicago&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivian Maier's Chicago</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Vivian-Maiers-Chicago/20364/</link>
      <description>10-07-2012 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
The Chicago History Museum brings to life Chicago as seen by photographer Vivian Maier. For the first time Maier's Chicago work will be presented at larger-than-life scale, vividly documenting Chicago places and faces in the loop, the city's west side and the northern suburbs during the 1960s and 70s.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Chicago History Museum&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Behind Door Number 3?</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Whats-Behind-Door-Number-3/23332/</link>
      <description>02-11-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Double Door, the historic rock venue that has hosted acts such as The Rolling Stones and Smashing Pumpkins, is now home to Chicago's most exciting new comedy show. They've renovated their downstairs space, and will host a FREE weekly comedy show featuring the best of Chicago's burgeoning alternative comedy scene. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;What's Behind Door Number 3&lt;/i&gt; is already becoming a &amp;quot;must-see&amp;quot; staple of Chicago's vibrant comedy scene. Each week the show features Chicago's foremost stand-up comedians, alongside the city's top-rated variety acts, and a topical news segment from the writers of the cult-favorite satire site &lt;i&gt;The Whiskey Journal&lt;/i&gt;. Hosted by the powerhouse team of Rob Wilson and Jamie Campbell, with a live house-band, and the folks of &amp;iexcl;Awesomonster! recording the show for their podcast, this show is far from your typical comedy fare. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yinka Shonibare, MBE</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Yinka-Shonibare-MBE/24588/</link>
      <description>06-17-2014 to 10-31-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This summer, the Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago presents the London-based artist Yinka Shonibare MBE, the next artist for the annual plaza series. Shonibare's installation premieres three sculptures from his new &lt;i&gt;Wind Series&lt;/i&gt;. Roughly twenty feet high, each monumental sculpture captures the movement of a billowing bolt of fabric, with designs inspired by the sails of ships, and patterns derived from Dutchwax fabric, or &amp;quot;African&amp;quot; batik. Shonibare works with these iconic fabrics to consider how signs of national or ethnic identity are culturally constructed. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
MCA Chicago's Plaza Project is part of the MCA's ongoing commitment to extending art into the community and enlivening Chicago's landscape with contemporary art beyond the museum's walls. Yinka Shonibare MBE is the fourth artist to be chosen for the MCA Chicago Plaza Project, which has previously featured work by Mark Handforth (2011), Martin Creed (2012), and Amanda Ross-Ho (2013). &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Installation view, MCA Chicago Plaza Project: Yinka Shonibare, MBE. June 16-October 2014. Photo: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 100s on the One and a Half</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/100-100s-on-the-One-and-a-Half/24087/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 08-24-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Shane Huffman is swimming to the Moon. If ignorance of the laws of nature is the basis of superstition, there's an element of deliberate superstition in Huffman's willful revision of cosmic order. Huffman reinvests interplanetary space, drained of mystery by the imposed order of cosmological description, with something &amp;quot;extra and other.&amp;quot; Using photography as an investigative process that works with three core phenomena, light, space-time and movement, he explores the individual as a participator in cosmic order rather than mere observer and parasite in &lt;i&gt;100 100s on the One and a Half: Shane Huffman&lt;/i&gt;. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Michigan Ave. Galleries on the 1st Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addendum</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Addendum/24712/</link>
      <description>07-25-2014 to 08-15-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Chicago Artists Coalition presents &lt;i&gt;Addendum&lt;/i&gt;, a group exhibition in association with the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.soapfactory.org/"&gt;Soap Factory&lt;/a&gt; as part of the Coalition's Midwest Artist Exchange.  &lt;i&gt;Addendum&lt;/i&gt; will comprise, per definition, the things which must be added, suggesting that the originating exhibition was neither complete, fixed or perfect. Far from it, in fact, as , , , (pronounced &amp;quot;comma comma comma&amp;quot;) asked of its artists to experiment, embrace uncertainty and trust the potential of their work in the context of a multi-dimensional group exhibition that could never speak fully to each artist's complex and rigorous practice. &lt;i&gt;Addendum&lt;/i&gt; begins to do just that by including, ad hoc, additional images, objects, gestures and performance that provide a more complete representation of many of the artists that made up the , , , exhibition, while simultaneously further problematizing the original survey.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo:&amp;nbsp;Once Around, Peter Happel Christian, 2014, bundle of 365 sheets of gelatin silver paper, rope, one calendar year (Jan. 1, 2013 - Dec.31, 2014)&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adelheid Mers: Enter the Matrix</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Adelheid-Mers-Enter-the-Matrix/24088/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 08-24-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
From studio critique, a mode of conversation about art works, Adelheid Mers has evolved a generative, productive method of talking about other issues as well, by diagramming them onto her Fractal 3-Line Matrix. In this exhibit, &lt;i&gt;Adelheid Mers: Enter the Matrix&lt;/i&gt;, she presents diagrams of conversations with artists about their work, visualizations of arts ecologies and the first iteration of Face Cloud, a cooperation with programmer Robert Woodley. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Blank Matrix Whiteboards will be available for ad hoc diagramming sessions with the public in the adjacent Garland Gallery. Mers will also utilize Garland Gallery as an open studio. Through her residency project, Mers invites the public to participate in her artistic process.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Michigan Ave. Galleries on the 1st Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN GONE ~ Miller &amp; Shellabarger</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/AGAIN-GONE-Miller-Shellabarger/24089/</link>
      <description>04-26-2014 to 08-24-2014 - In &lt;i&gt;AGAIN GONE ~ Miller &amp;amp; Shellabarger&lt;/i&gt;, Miller &amp;amp; Shellabarger use gunpowder and black oil sunflower seeds to outline their bodies and hands. Both materials hold immense amounts of energy, even when distilled into diminutive containers, and are utilized for their rich metaphorical connotation. One is used to feed the flame. The other is left as feed. The flash of gunpowder produces an afterimage, visible not when closing one's eyes, but sprawled out across paper. The explosive marks of smoke and flame trace that which is gone. &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Michigan Ave. Galleries on the 1st Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Junkie’s Live Music Stage</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/American-Junkies-Live-Music-Stage/22313/</link>
      <description>06-05-2013 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
American Junkie's second level will come to life as the stage ignites every Wednesday to include some of the country's most sought-after performers along with up-and-coming artists.  Live sets from bands spanning across genres from pop to punk, rock and country will be knocking the retractable roof off! &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Whether music-goers are seated at the 360 degree bar or lounging at one of the booths, the high fidelity quality of the sound system ensures clarity and precision for any beat. Each live performance will perform on American Junkie's hand-crafted 8 foot by 16 foot stage.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ann Worthing - All is Beauty</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Ann-Worthing-All-is-Beauty/24798/</link>
      <description>07-18-2014 to 08-22-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The colorful flourishes and calm spaces in &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.annworthing.com/"&gt;Ann Worthing&lt;/a&gt;'s paintings invite a unique sort of looking that allows the viewer to explore and discover each individual world with the curiosity of an aimless wanderer. Landscapes unfold slowly as different textures, figures, and gestures flicker into and out of view, and the viewer's presence in the space shifts between individual and communal; the wanderer is at once a single unit in a network of other separate fragments, and a thread in a fluid, dynamic whole. From this duality, the paintings gain asense of constant movement, where even the most serene and static elements--tree trunk, country road, horizon--refuse stillness.  Each form appears to move at its own pace, and the viewer remains free to navigate the dips and turns at a different speed altogether.  Rather than producing discord, this freedom of movement encourages a subtle yet powerful fluidity, which ultimately creates in each piece a cohesive cadence.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Packer Schopf Gallery&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apes of Wrath</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Apes-of-Wrath/24507/</link>
      <description>06-21-2014 In the world of high stakes, we become a more heightened version of ourselves, which can sometimes resemble more simian behavior than human. From unitard sporting performance artists, an intimate encounter with robot culture and the primal effects of downsizing, &lt;i&gt;Apes of Wrath&lt;/i&gt; embraces the dark and light sides of our human devolution.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Veteran Chicago-based director &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/2034/"&gt;Jen Ellison&lt;/a&gt; leads returning cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1794/"&gt;Carisa Barreca&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1793/"&gt;Brooke Breit&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1835/"&gt;Punam Patel&lt;/a&gt; with new cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/2035/"&gt;Eddie Mujica&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/2086/"&gt;Asher Perlman&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1988/"&gt;Tim Ryder&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1743/"&gt;Alex Kliner&lt;/a&gt; is back at the piano as the Musical Director and Composer and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1392/"&gt;Kyle Anderson&lt;/a&gt; returns as Stage Manager. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of The Second City. Credit:&amp;nbsp;Todd Rosenberg &lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenue Q</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Avenue-Q/24319/</link>
      <description>04-23-2014 to 10-26-2014 - Mercury Theater Chicago presents Chicago's home-grown version of the hilarious Broadway musical &lt;i&gt;Avenue Q&lt;/i&gt;.  Winner of the Tony &amp;quot;Triple Crown&amp;quot; for Best Musical, Best Score and Best Book in 2004, &lt;i&gt;Avenue Q&lt;/i&gt; is part flesh, part felt, and packed with heart.  The production will be led by Jeff Award winners L. Walter Stearns (Director), Eugene Dizon (Musical Direction), and Kevin Bellie (Choreography) and features custom made puppets by Russ Walko.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
A racy cross between &lt;i&gt;South Park&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Sesame Street&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Avenue Q&lt;/i&gt; is a modern musical focusing on a group of unique 20-somethings making their way in the big city, seeking their purpose in life.  &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos by MICHAEL BROSILOW&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bach House Tour</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Bach-House-Tour/24501/</link>
      <description>05-07-2014 to 09-24-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Step inside one of Frank Lloyd Wright's more intimate homes on the Frank Lloyd Wright Trust's new tour of the Emil Bach House in Chicago, meticulously restored to its original 1915 appearance by Harboe Architects.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Built for Emil Bach, president of Chicago's Bach Brick Co, the house was executed between Wright's return from Europe in 1911 and his departure to Japan in 1916 to oversee construction of the Imperial Hotel. &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
In contrast to the expansive, open Prairie houses Wright designed prior to his European sojourn, the Bach House is strongly centered with self-contained built-ins and striking window designs. It looks toward the architect's future stylistic directions in its crisp geometry and efficient scale.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo:&amp;nbsp;The Emil Bach House (1915), Frank Lloyd Wright. Photo Credit: Courtesy of Frank Lloyd Wright Trust. Photographer: James Caulfield&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandits &amp; Heroes, Poets &amp; Saints</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Bandits-Heroes-Poets-Saints/24043/</link>
      <description>05-09-2014 to 08-17-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Bandits &amp;amp; Heroes, Poets &amp;amp; Saints: Popular Art of the Northeast of Brazil&lt;/i&gt; tells the story of how African, European and indigenous cultural traditions have interacted over a period of more than 500 years to form the distinctive culture of this fascinating area of the largest country in South America. Brazil is home to one of the largest populations of African descendants in the world, with more than 75 million people. Currently, most of Brazil's population lives in the Northeast of Brazil where centuries of African, European, and Amerindian cultures have mingled to create a mixture of conventions that help in shaping Latin American heritage. &lt;i&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Exhibit Segments&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Bandits &amp;amp; Heroes, Poets &amp;amp; Saints&lt;/i&gt; includes nearly 200 works of art by more than 50 artists. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;The first segment, &lt;b&gt;The Land and Its People&lt;/b&gt;, reflects on the history of slavery in Brazil, from the rich plantations that produced a wealthy amount of agricultural produce along the coast to the rugged landscape of the inhospitable dry backlands of the fugitive slave communities.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;The second segment, &lt;b&gt;Expressions of Faith&lt;/b&gt;, explores the African-Brazilian religion of Candomble which combines traditional African roots and Roman Catholicism, while also exploring the evangelical faith of the Northeast.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;The third segment, &lt;b&gt;Poetry, Celebration and Song&lt;/b&gt;, focuses on folk legends and popular festivals of the Nordestinos (People of the Northeast). Also featured in this segment is Literature de Cordel (Literature on a String), which is a popular form of poetry, retelling stories and legends.&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Harvest Film Festival</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Black-Harvest-Film-Festival/22065/</link>
      <description>08-01-2014 to 08-28-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The Black Harvest Film Festival is our city's largest and longest-running Black film festival and the Gene Siskel Film Center's most vibrant annual showcase featuring provocative films that tell stories, spark lively discussions, and address issues relating to the experiences from the African diaspora. A number of films are made by Chicago directors and feature post-show Q&amp;amp;As.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Fun fact: Black Harvest Film Festival celebrates its 20th year in 2014! &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Man Group</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Blue-Man-Group/20245/</link>
      <description>06-01-2012 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Experience a multi-sensory show that fuses theatrical spectacle and original music with comedy, art, vaudeville and science!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo:&amp;nbsp;Ken Howard &amp;copy;BMP&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMO Harris Chicago Works: Zachary Cahill</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/BMO-Harris-Chicago-Works-Zachary-Cahill/23484/</link>
      <description>04-29-2014 to 09-28-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
For his exhibit, Cahill presents &lt;i&gt;Snow:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;USSA 2012: The Wellness Center&lt;/i&gt;, the third phase of his project exploring the role institutions play in society. His earlier parts include&lt;i&gt; USSA 2012: The Orphanage Project&lt;/i&gt; (2011), where he re-imagined an orphanage and a gift shop, &lt;i&gt;USSA 2012: The People's Palace's Gift Shop&lt;/i&gt; (2012), and a site-specific banner project &lt;i&gt;USSA 2012: Wellness Center: Idyllic -- affair of the heart&lt;/i&gt; (2013). &lt;i&gt;For Snow&lt;/i&gt;, Cahill approximates a turn of the century sanatorium somewhere in northern Europe. Visitors are invited to enter an actual and fictional space divided into three sections -- a welcome center, a library, and an art gallery -- where Cahill's paintings, sculptures, and writings explore psychological states. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
By simulating a place of refuge within the museum, &lt;i&gt;Snow&lt;/i&gt; navigates the costs and benefits of social withdrawal as necessitated by individual or collective trauma. Drawing on a variety of source material, including Thomas Mann's novel &lt;i&gt;The Magic Mountain&lt;/i&gt;; the Outlook Hotel from Stanley Kubrick's film adaptation of Stephen King's novel &lt;i&gt;The Shining&lt;/i&gt;; and the tradition of Northern Romantic and German Expressionist painting, Cahill considers the role of art in society at the beginning of the 21st century. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: Zachary Cahill, The Future, 2013. Courtesy of the artist and USSA 2012.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabaret Lunch Cruises – Spirit of Chicago</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Cabaret-Lunch-Cruises-Spirit-of-Chicago/24431/</link>
      <description>06-24-2014 to 08-26-2014 - This two-hour cruise along Chicago's magnificent lakefront is perfect for an afternoon getaway, a birthday, church group, entertaining out-of-town guests, you name it.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Enjoy this truly interactive entertainment experience with the Spirit of Chicago Cabaret Show. They will delight you with a broad repertoire - everything from sing-along show tunes to jazz standards. Along the way they will incorporate fascinating facts about the famous Chicago skyline. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Entertainment Cruises &amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte Salomon: Life? Or Theater?</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Charlotte-Salomon-Life-Or-Theater/24442/</link>
      <description>06-19-2014 to 09-21-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
In the early years of World War II, Charlotte Salomon - a 23-year-old Jewish artist from Berlin - fled to the south of France where she shut herself into a hotel room and spent two years feverishly painting the history of her life. She called it &lt;i&gt;Life? or Theater?: A Play With Music&lt;/i&gt;, an astounding body of over 1,300 powerfully drawn and expressively colored gouache paintings conceived as an operetta on paper. Salomon used images, musical cues, dialogue and commentary to tell a compelling coming-of-age story set amidst increasing Nazi oppression. Shortly after completing &lt;i&gt;Life? or Theater?&lt;/i&gt;, the pregnant 26-year-old was transported to Auschwitz and killed. Her singular creation and only major work survived and stands as a testament to Salomon's life and artistic vision.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition of nearly 300 paintings from &lt;i&gt;Life? or Theater?&lt;/i&gt; offers a rare, first-hand opportunity to witness this amazing masterpiece.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Collection Jewish Historical Museum, Amsterdam. Charlotte Salomon Foundation. Charlotte Salomon&amp;reg;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte's Web</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Charlottes-Web/23899/</link>
      <description>07-11-2014 to 08-17-2014 - The favorite on every child's bookshelf, &lt;i&gt;Charlotte's Web&lt;/i&gt;, comes to the stage! When Wilbur is saved and sent to live on farm, he finds a new unexpected family. Follow this piggy hero as he grows from being the runt of the litter to &amp;quot;Some Pig&amp;quot; with the help of a remarkable spider, Charlotte. Join Wilbur, Charlotte, Templeton the Rat, and all the farmyard friends at the State Fair this summer in &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.emeraldcitytheatre.com/"&gt;Emerald City Theatre&lt;/a&gt;'s &lt;i&gt;Charlotte's Web&lt;/i&gt;!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHGO DSGN</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/CHGO-DSGN/24083/</link>
      <description>05-31-2014 to 11-02-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;CHGO DSGN: Recent Object and Graphic Design. Curated by Rick Valicenti.  &lt;/i&gt;is a major exhibition of recent object and graphic design by 100+ of the city's leading designers. Chicago has long been regarded as an international center for design, and this retrospective celebrates the region's creative and innovative spirit. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibit is located in the Exhibit Hall on the 4th Floor of the Chicago Cultural Center. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;CENTRAL STANDARD TIMING, CST-01 Wristwatch &lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;CODY HUDSON, Vibes Melt Down 2043&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;ROMAIN ANDR&amp;Eacute; AND MICHAEL SAVONA, The Way of the Shovel Scratch-off Poster.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Images courtesy MCA Chicago. Mark Dion, Shovel illustration on the top layer, and Tony Tasset, uncovered photograph.&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;MATT WIZINSKY, CloudWriter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Cubs v Milwaukee Brewers</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Cubs-v-Milwaukee-Brewers/23149/</link>
      <description>08-11-2014 to 08-14-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
See the Chicago Cubs play against the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://milwaukee.brewers.mlb.com/index.jsp?c_id=mil"&gt;Milwaukee Brewers&lt;/a&gt; August 11-14 at The Friendly Confines!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Celebrate Wrigley Field's 100th Birthday&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The 2014 season marks Wrigley Field's 100th birthday! The team will celebrate the ballpark's rich century of history during 10 decade-themed homestands complete with historic player uniforms, specialty food offerings, promotional items and entertainment. Go to &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.mlb.com/chc/wrigleyfield100/"&gt;WrigleyField100.com&lt;/a&gt; to learn more. Festivities include:&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Wrigley Field's 100 Great Moments presented by Budweiser&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Historic Bobbleheads&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Throwback Uniforms&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Retro Toys&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://chicago.cubs.mlb.com/chc/ticketing/specialevents.jsp"&gt;Special Events Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Dining Through the Decades&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Historic Guests and Game Entertainment&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://chicago.cubs.mlb.com/chc/fan_forum/cubs_authentics.jsp"&gt;Ballpark&amp;nbsp;D&amp;eacute;cor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Commemorative Ticket Designs&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Farmers Markets</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Farmers-Markets/21668/</link>
      <description>05-10-2014 to 10-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Our city's neighborhoods host annual farmers markets May to October! With each location offering various fruits, vegetables, plants, flowers and more, there's a market for everyone to enjoy. Check the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/dca/supp_info/farmers_market0.html"&gt;Seasonality Chart&lt;/a&gt; to see when your favorite produce is available!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Community Markets&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
New for 2014, some markets will become Community Markets. This is a new concept being introduced, as a market is reflective of the neighborhood it serves. Each market will have what you would expect at a typical farmers market with items like fresh produce, with the addition of music programming and non-food vendors like local artisans - adding a unique vibe to each market and expanding the neighborhood's cultural assets.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Night Markets&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
These will be unique, multi-faceted events which will include live performances and arts &amp;amp; crafts, with local artisans and local restaurants participating. &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Tuesday: Fulton Randolph Market District/Union Park Community Market&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Wednesday: Devon Night Market&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Thursday: Argyle Night Market&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Downtown Markets&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Tuesday: Federal Plaza, Museum of Contemporary Art&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Thursday: Daley Plaza, Willis Tower&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;b&gt;Neighborhood Markets&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Tuesday: Columbus Park, Lincoln Square, Fulton Randolph District/Union Park Community Market&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Wednesday: La Follette Park, Pullman, Devon Community Night Market, Ford City Mall&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Thursday: Argyle Night Market, Austin Town Hall, Hyde Park&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Saturday: Bridgeport, Englewood/Anchor House, Division Street, Lincoln Park, North Center, Printers Row, Southport Market, West Humboldt Park&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Sunday: Beverly, South Shore - Rainbow Beach Park, Garfield Park Conservatory &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;City of Chicago, Department of Cultural Affairs and Special Events&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Landmarks Before the Lens</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Landmarks-Before-the-Lens/18473/</link>
      <description>12-08-2011 to 12-31-2020 - This ongoing exhibition&amp;nbsp;presented by the Commission on Chicago Landmarks features 72 black and white photographs of 24 landmarks and historic districts by Richard Nickel, Barbara Crane, Bob Thall, and Stephen Beal.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Shakespeare in the Parks</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-Shakespeare-in-the-Parks/19626/</link>
      <description>07-18-2014 to 08-17-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Chicago Shakespeare Theater presents &lt;i&gt;A Midsummer Night's Dream &lt;/i&gt;for its 2014 Chicago Shakespeare in the Parks season!&amp;nbsp;A specially equipped truck will roll into parks around the city, a stage will unfold, and a company of professional actors will share the delight of Shakespeare with families and neighbors of all ages. &#xD;
In its third year, Chicago Shakespeare in the Parks returns to 18 communities, truly establishing the program as a Chicago summer tradition.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
In&lt;i&gt; A Midsummer Night's Dream&lt;/i&gt;, a popular Shakespearean comedy, a quartet of mismatched lovers, a gaggle of hapless actors and mischievous sprites cross paths with the king and queen of the fairies, entangled in their own domestic dispute. Audiences will be transported to an extraordinary wood brimming with paramours and possibilities where the inexplicable magic of falling in love-and the wonder of waking up from the sweetest of dreams-is discovered.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This tour is made possible by a partnership between Chicago Shakespeare Theater, the City of Chicago, Chicago Park District, Boeing and BMO Harris Bank.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoshakes.com/plays_and_events/parks2014/parks2014whereandwhen"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 18-19: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.navypier.com/about/ov_gateway.html"&gt;Gateway Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 20: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/garfield-park-conservatory/"&gt;Garfield Park Conservatory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 22: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Tuley-Park/#.U3okDihDNSY"&gt;Tuley Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 23-24: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Dvorak-Park/"&gt;Dvorak Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 25-26: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Loyola-Park/"&gt;Loyola Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 27: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/washington-park/"&gt;Washington Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 29: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Riis-Park/"&gt;Riis Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 30: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Piotrowski-Park/"&gt;Piotrowski Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;July 31: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Gage-Park/"&gt;Gage Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 1: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Hamilton-Park/"&gt;Hamilton Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 2-3: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/wilson-frank-j-park/"&gt;Frank J. Wilson Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 6-7: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/humboldtpark/"&gt;Humboldt Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 8-9: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Welles-Park/"&gt;Welles Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 10: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/columbus-park/"&gt;Columbus Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 12: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Marquette-Park/"&gt;Marquette Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 13: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Ridge-Park/"&gt;Ridge Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 14-15: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Ridge-Park/#.U3olLihDNSY"&gt;South Shore Cultural Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;August 16-17: &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.chicagoparkdistrict.com/parks/Eckhart-Park/"&gt;Eckhart Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos by Chuck Osgood&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago: City of Big Data</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicago-City-of-Big-Data/24752/</link>
      <description>06-19-2014 to 10-01-2015 - Did you know data has become a 21st century design material? Architects, planners, engineers and citizens increasingly use data to understand urban issues and spark design innovation. This explosion of digital information, known as &amp;quot;Big Data,&amp;quot; encompasses everything from data collected by environmental sensors to messages on social media. This new exhibition reveals the potential of urban data and offers a new perspective on Chicago and cities everywhere. Visitors can explore interactive displays, recreated sections of the city and get unique views into your own personal data. &lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Chicago Architecture Foundation&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicagoisms</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Chicagoisms/23889/</link>
      <description>04-05-2014 to 01-04-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Throughout its history the city of Chicago has inspired myriad urban and architectural innovations, many of which have had far-reaching influence. The collection of the Art Institute's Department of Architecture has extensive holdings on work within the region of Chicago, representing the important innovations, theoretical approaches, and architectural movements spurred by the city's development. This exhibition surveys Chicago's rich urban history and explores contemporary approaches to five Chicagoisms-key historical principles that have powered the city's distinctive evolution.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit:&amp;nbsp;Installation view of Chicagoisms at the Art Institute of Chicago, April 5, 2014-January 4, 2015.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cirque Shanghai: Warriors</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Cirque-Shanghai-Warriors/24073/</link>
      <description>05-21-2014 to 08-31-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Cirque Shanghai&lt;/i&gt; is proud to return this summer to Navy Pier with a brand new show, &lt;i&gt;Cirque Shanghai: Warriors&lt;/i&gt;. This latest installment of &lt;i&gt;Cirque Shanghai&lt;/i&gt; combines the impressive acrobatics audiences have enjoyed in the past with the martial prowess of Chinese Kung Fu and Wu Shu masters. The result is powerful display of athleticism and the mastery of disciplines that formed the backbone of military might in ancient China for thousands of years.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This summer's production of &lt;i&gt;Cirque Shanghai: Warriors&lt;/i&gt; brings an extraordinary line-up of thrilling acts to the stage, including The Kinetic Poles, the powerful Water Meteor and the heart-pounding Pageant of Arms. Returning to the production from last year is the fate-tempting &lt;i&gt;Wheel of Destiny&lt;/i&gt;, and China's premier daredevil steel-globe motorcycle troupe, &lt;i&gt;Imperial Thunder&lt;/i&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of&amp;nbsp;Carol Fox &amp;amp; Associates &lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Lights Night Tour</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/City-Lights-Night-Tour/24322/</link>
      <description>05-01-2014 to 09-30-2014 - The City Lights Night Tour allows passengers to view the city at night in all of its lit up glory. Highlights will include the John Hancock Building, &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/things-to-do/tours-and-attractions/millennium-park/"&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/articles/view/NAVY-PIER-DAZZLES-DAY-AND-NIGHT/84/"&gt;Navy Pier&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/neighborhoods-and-communities/intro/magnificent-mile/"&gt;Magnificent Mile&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossings and Dwellings</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Crossings-and-Dwellings/24758/</link>
      <description>07-19-2014 to 10-19-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Using art, historical maps, broadsheets, books, liturgical objects, and textiles, &lt;i&gt;Crossings and Dwellings: Restored Jesuits, Women Religious, American Experience, 1814-2014&lt;/i&gt; tells the story of 19th-century European Jesuits and women religious who arrived on the country's expanding western frontier to serve both indigenous and immigrant populations. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
This exhibition includes liturgical and educational treasures, such as globes by Willem Jansz Blaeu (Dutch, 1571-1638), drawings by Nicolas Point, S.J. (French, 1799-1868), maps by Pierre Jean De Smet, S.J. (Belgian, 1801-1873), the chalice of S&amp;eacute;bastien-Louis Meurin, S.J. (French, 1707-1777), a cope made by St. Rose Philippine Duchesne, RSCJ (French, 1769-1852), and vestments created by indigenous people and presented to De Smet. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
The exhibition will also examine the pioneering role of the Religious of the Sacred Heart (RSCJ) and the Sisters of Charity of the Blessed Virgin Mary (BVM) in building Chicago educational institutions, including several schools in Holy Family Parish, Immaculata High School, and Mundelein College.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Crossings and Dwellings&lt;/i&gt; commemorates both the 200th anniversary of the Restoration of the Society of Jesus (1814-2014) and a century of women's education at Loyola-Mundelein (1914-2014).&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depraved New World</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Depraved-New-World/23351/</link>
      <description>03-27-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Ever wonder what people are really thinking? Maybe its positive and sweet. Maybe its weird and dirty. From musical orgies, blind dates and the innocent beginning of an international email scam, &lt;i&gt;Depraved New World&lt;/i&gt; takes you on a wild ride to see what's happening behind the eyes of the beholder. &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Returning to The Second City Mainstage, prolific Jeff Award-winning director &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1980/"&gt;Mick Napier&lt;/a&gt; leads returning cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1515/"&gt;Steve Waltien&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1735/"&gt;Tawny Newsome&lt;/a&gt; with new cast members &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1977/"&gt;Chelsea Devantez&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1978/"&gt;John Hartman&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1550/"&gt;Mike Kosinski&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1979/"&gt;Emily Walker&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/1981/"&gt;Jesse Case&lt;/a&gt; takes his place behind the piano as the new Musical Director and Composer and &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.secondcity.com/about/people/castbio/113/"&gt;Craig Taylor&lt;/a&gt; returns to the booth as Stage Manager.  &amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos by TODD ROSENBERG&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destination Solar System</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Destination-Solar-System/23847/</link>
      <description>05-16-2014 &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Destination Solar System&lt;/i&gt; is a live show that takes adventurous space explorers on an immersive tour of the Solar System. Set in the future, &lt;i&gt;Destination Solar System&lt;/i&gt; flies audiences from one end of the Solar System to the other in under 30 minutes! From sizzling solar flares on the Sun to liquid methane lakes on Saturn's moon, Titan, tours to the hottest hot spots and the coldest, stormiest and most spectacular sights in the Solar System will launch daily from the Adler's &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.adlerplanetarium.org/shows/"&gt;Grainger Sky Theater&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo courtesy of Adler Planetarium&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthly Delights</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Earthly-Delights/23485/</link>
      <description>06-28-2014 to 11-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Earthly Delights&lt;/i&gt; features the work of artists who rejected one of the central tenets of modernism - the elimination of content and external references - in favor of embracing the decorative, feminine, and playful. This irreverence takes a variety of forms. Swiss artist Balthus remained a committed realist, even though he worked during the time of Surrealism. Michelangelo Pistoletto turned to history painting, intentionally referencing styles and forms considered pass&amp;eacute;. Lynda Benglis, challenged the feminist movement and persisted in the production of non-representative sculpture rather than painting. Carol Bove and Marc Camille Chaimowicz produced objects that exuded sensuality and intimacy; while Nick Cave, Lari Pittman, and Yinka Shonibare exhibit a visible reverence for the popular, accessible, and decorative. Despite the frivolity and humor present in these works, many of the artists exhibited are deeply involved with issues of gender, identity, and politics. This is not 'art for art's sake,' but a belief in the transcendent power of beauty.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photo credit: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago. Lari Pittman, Untitled #14, 2003. Collection Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, Joseph and Jory Shapiro Fund by exchange.&amp;copy; 2003 Lari Pittman Photo: Nathan Keay, &amp;copy; MCA Chicago.&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enduring Style: Practice Makes Perfect</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Enduring-Style-Practice-Makes-Perfect/24682/</link>
      <description>06-11-2014 to 09-05-2014 - Willis Tower is currently holding its first fashion exhibition, &lt;i&gt;Enduring Style: Practice Makes Perfect&lt;/i&gt;, in partnership with the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.colum.edu/Admissions/Programs/Fashion.php"&gt;Fashion Studies Department at Columbia College Chicago&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Located in the ground floor lobby of Willis Tower, the exhibition showcases:&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;ul&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;38 fashion ensembles enhanced by 14 large-scale fashion photographs&lt;/b&gt; focusing on the enduring nature of high-quality design&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;Columbia College's partnership with the &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://eyeonindia.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eye on India Festival&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, adds &lt;b&gt;three towering 23-foot santos figures showcasing 18&lt;/b&gt; zero-waste, modern design interpretations of India's traditional sari. &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
	&lt;li&gt;All designs are by students and graduates of the Fashion Studies Department.  &lt;/li&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#xD;
&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Columbia College Chicago&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireworks Dinner Cruises – Mystic Blue</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Fireworks-Dinner-Cruises-Mystic-Blue/24434/</link>
      <description>05-24-2014 to 08-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
See Chicago fireworks aboard Mystic Blue on Wednesday and Saturday evenings this summer. You'll get tasty treats, hot DJ beats and the best views of the skyline and &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/articles/view/NAVY-PIER-DAZZLES-DAY-AND-NIGHT/84/"&gt;Navy Pier&lt;/a&gt; Fireworks display. Mystic Blue gives you the best views of the Fireworks.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Entertainment Cruises&lt;/i&gt; &#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireworks Dinner Cruises – Odyssey</title>
      <link>http://www.choosechicago.com/event/Fireworks-Dinner-Cruises-Odyssey/24435/</link>
      <description>05-24-2014 to 08-30-2014 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Savor creative appetizers and entr&amp;eacute;es prepared fresh onboard daily by our Executive Chef. Sample mouth-watering desserts. Dance or relax and take in the views; it's your cruise. Make your way to their lit dance floor and let their upscale DJ entertain you. Or, head topside and sip a cocktail as you listen to their live guitarist on Wednesday and Saturday Dinners. Relax with some light music and take in stunning skyline views from Chicago's best rooftop lounge. Near the end of your cruise, you will want to go outside onto one of Odyssey's many observation decks. The sky above the lakefront will fill with spectacular displays of color and the thundering sounds of &lt;a href="http://www.choosechicago.com/articles/view/NAVY-PIER-DAZZLES-DAY-AND-NIGHT/84/"&gt;Navy Pier&lt;/a&gt;'s outstanding fireworks show.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;i&gt;Photos courtesy of Entertainment Cruises &amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>